-DOCSTART- - - O

FILE 21 25 O
PHOTO 26 31 O
: 32 33 O
An 34 36 O
Iranian 37 44 I-MISC
flag 45 49 O
flutters 50 58 O
in 59 61 O
front 62 67 O
of 68 70 O
the 71 74 O
International 75 88 I-ORG
Atomic 89 95 I-ORG
Energy 96 102 I-ORG
Agency 103 109 I-ORG
( 110 111 O
IAEA 112 116 I-ORG
) 117 118 O
headquarters 119 131 O
in 132 134 O
Vienna 135 141 I-LOC
, 142 143 O
Austria 144 151 I-LOC
September 152 161 O
9 162 163 O
, 164 165 O
2019 166 170 O
. 171 172 O

REUTERS 174 181 I-ORG
/ 182 183 O
Leonhard 184 192 I-PER
Foeger 193 199 I-PER

PARIS 201 206 I-LOC
( 207 208 O
Reuters 209 216 I-ORG
) 217 218 O
- 219 220 O
France 221 227 I-LOC
, 228 229 O
Germany 230 237 I-LOC
and 238 241 O
Britain 242 249 I-LOC
said 250 254 O
on 255 257 O
Monday 258 264 O
they 265 269 O
were 270 274 O
alarmed 275 282 O
by 283 285 O
an 286 288 O
Iranian 289 296 I-MISC
announcement 297 309 O
that 310 314 O
it 315 317 O
intended 318 326 O
to 327 329 O
install 330 337 O
additional 338 348 O
, 349 350 O
advanced 351 359 O
uranium-enriching 360 377 O
centrifuges 378 389 O
and 390 393 O
by 394 396 O
legislation 397 408 O
that 409 413 O
could 414 419 O
expand 420 426 O
its 427 430 O
nuclear 431 438 O
programme 439 448 O
. 449 450 O

“ 452 453 O
If 454 456 O
Iran 457 461 I-LOC
is 462 464 O
serious 465 472 O
about 473 478 O
preserving 479 489 O
a 490 491 O
space 492 497 O
for 498 501 O
diplomacy 502 511 O
, 512 513 O
it 514 516 O
must 517 521 O
not 522 525 O
implement 526 535 O
these 536 541 O
steps 542 547 O
, 548 549 O
” 550 551 O
the 552 555 O
three 556 561 O
powers 562 568 O
, 569 570 O
who 571 574 O
along 575 580 O
with 581 585 O
China 586 591 I-LOC
and 592 595 O
Russia 596 602 I-LOC
are 603 606 O
party 607 612 O
to 613 615 O
a 616 617 O
2015 618 622 O
nuclear 623 630 O
containment 631 642 O
deal 643 647 O
with 648 652 O
Tehran 653 659 I-LOC
, 660 661 O
known 662 667 O
as 668 670 O
the 671 674 O
JCPoA 675 680 I-MISC
, 681 682 O
said 683 687 O
in 688 690 O
a 691 692 O
joint 693 698 O
statement 699 708 O
. 709 710 O

A 712 713 O
confidential 714 726 O
International 727 740 I-ORG
Atomic 741 747 I-ORG
Energy 748 754 I-ORG
Agency 755 761 I-ORG
report 762 768 O
obtained 769 777 O
by 778 780 O
Reuters 781 788 I-ORG
said 789 793 O
Iran 794 798 I-LOC
plans 799 804 O
to 805 807 O
install 808 815 O
three 816 821 O
more 822 826 O
cascades 827 835 O
, 836 837 O
or 838 840 O
clusters 841 849 O
, 850 851 O
of 852 854 O
advanced 855 863 O
IR-2m 864 869 I-MISC
centrifuges 870 881 O
in 882 884 O
its 885 888 O
enrichment 889 899 O
plant 900 905 O
at 906 908 O
Natanz 909 915 I-LOC
, 916 917 O
which 918 923 O
was 924 927 O
built 928 933 O
underground 934 945 O
apparently 946 956 O
to 957 959 O
withstand 960 969 O
any 970 973 O
aerial 974 980 O
bombardment 981 992 O
. 993 994 O

Iran 996 1000 I-LOC
’s 1001 1003 O
nuclear 1004 1011 O
deal 1012 1016 O
with 1017 1021 O
major 1022 1027 O
powers 1028 1034 O
says 1035 1039 O
Tehran 1040 1046 I-LOC
can 1047 1050 O
only 1051 1055 O
use 1056 1059 O
first-generation 1060 1076 O
IR-1 1077 1081 I-MISC
centrifuges 1082 1093 O
, 1094 1095 O
which 1096 1101 O
refine 1102 1108 O
uranium 1109 1116 O
much 1117 1121 O
more 1122 1126 O
slowly 1127 1133 O
, 1134 1135 O
at 1136 1138 O
Natanz 1139 1145 I-LOC
and 1146 1149 O
that 1150 1154 O
those 1155 1160 O
are 1161 1164 O
the 1165 1168 O
only 1169 1173 O
machines 1174 1182 O
with 1183 1187 O
which 1188 1193 O
Iran 1194 1198 I-LOC
may 1199 1202 O
accumulate 1203 1213 O
enriched 1214 1222 O
stocks 1223 1229 O
. 1230 1231 O

“ 1233 1234 O
Iran 1235 1239 I-LOC
’s 1240 1242 O
recent 1243 1249 O
announcement 1250 1262 O
to 1263 1265 O
the 1266 1269 O
IAEA 1270 1274 I-ORG
that 1275 1279 O
it 1280 1282 O
intends 1283 1290 O
to 1291 1293 O
install 1294 1301 O
an 1302 1304 O
additional 1305 1315 O
three 1316 1321 O
cascades 1322 1330 O
of 1331 1333 O
advanced 1334 1342 O
centrifuges 1343 1354 O
at 1355 1357 O
the 1358 1361 O
Fuel 1362 1366 I-LOC
Enrichment 1367 1377 I-LOC
Plant 1378 1383 I-LOC
in 1384 1386 O
Natanz 1387 1393 I-LOC
is 1394 1396 O
contrary 1397 1405 O
to 1406 1408 O
the 1409 1412 O
JCPoA 1413 1418 I-MISC
and 1419 1422 O
deeply 1423 1429 O
worrying 1430 1438 O
, 1439 1440 O
” 1441 1442 O
the 1443 1446 O
three 1447 1452 O
powers 1453 1459 O
said 1460 1464 O
of 1465 1467 O
the 1468 1471 O
U.N. 1472 1476 I-ORG
watchdog 1477 1485 O
report 1486 1492 O
, 1493 1494 O
which 1495 1500 O
has 1501 1504 O
yet 1505 1508 O
to 1509 1511 O
be 1512 1514 O
made 1515 1519 O
public 1520 1526 O
. 1527 1528 O

The 1530 1533 O
powers 1534 1540 O
further 1541 1548 O
said 1549 1553 O
a 1554 1555 O
new 1556 1559 O
law 1560 1563 O
obliging 1564 1572 O
Iran 1573 1577 I-LOC
’s 1578 1580 O
government 1581 1591 O
to 1592 1594 O
halt 1595 1599 O
U.N. 1600 1604 I-ORG
inspections 1605 1616 O
of 1617 1619 O
its 1620 1623 O
nuclear 1624 1631 O
sites 1632 1637 O
and 1638 1641 O
step 1642 1646 O
up 1647 1649 O
enrichment 1650 1660 O
beyond 1661 1667 O
the 1668 1671 O
deal 1672 1676 O
’s 1677 1679 O
limits 1680 1686 O
was 1687 1690 O
also 1691 1695 O
incompatible 1696 1708 O
with 1709 1713 O
the 1714 1717 O
accord 1718 1724 O
and 1725 1728 O
Iran 1729 1733 I-LOC
’s 1734 1736 O
wider 1737 1742 O
non-proliferation 1743 1760 O
commitments 1761 1772 O
. 1773 1774 O

“ 1776 1777 O
Such 1778 1782 O
a 1783 1784 O
move 1785 1789 O
would 1790 1795 O
jeopardise 1796 1806 O
our 1807 1810 O
shared 1811 1817 O
efforts 1818 1825 O
to 1826 1828 O
preserve 1829 1837 O
the 1838 1841 O
JCPOA 1842 1847 I-MISC
and 1848 1851 O
also 1852 1856 O
risks 1857 1862 O
compromising 1863 1875 O
the 1876 1879 O
important 1880 1889 O
opportunity 1890 1901 O
for 1902 1905 O
a 1906 1907 O
return 1908 1914 O
to 1915 1917 O
diplomacy 1918 1927 O
with 1928 1932 O
the 1933 1936 O
incoming 1937 1945 O
U.S. 1946 1950 I-LOC
administration 1951 1965 O
, 1966 1967 O
” 1968 1969 O
they 1970 1974 O
said 1975 1979 O
, 1980 1981 O
referring 1982 1991 O
to 1992 1994 O
Joe 1995 1998 I-PER
Biden 1999 2004 I-PER
, 2005 2006 O
who 2007 2010 O
defeated 2011 2019 O
President 2020 2029 O
Donald 2030 2036 I-PER
Trump 2037 2042 I-PER
in 2043 2045 O
the 2046 2049 O
Nov. 2050 2054 O
3 2055 2056 O
election 2057 2065 O
. 2066 2067 O

“ 2069 2070 O
A 2071 2072 O
return 2073 2079 O
to 2080 2082 O
the 2083 2086 O
JCPOA 2087 2092 I-MISC
would 2093 2098 O
also 2099 2103 O
be 2104 2106 O
beneficial 2107 2117 O
for 2118 2121 O
Iran 2122 2126 I-LOC
, 2127 2128 O
” 2129 2130 O
the 2131 2134 O
three 2135 2140 O
added 2141 2146 O
, 2147 2148 O
referring 2149 2158 O
to 2159 2161 O
Tehran 2162 2168 I-LOC
’s 2169 2171 O
decisions 2172 2181 O
to 2182 2184 O
reverse 2185 2192 O
some 2193 2197 O
of 2198 2200 O
its 2201 2204 O
nuclear 2205 2212 O
commitments 2213 2224 O
in 2225 2227 O
response 2228 2236 O
to 2237 2239 O
the 2240 2243 O
Trump 2244 2249 I-PER
administration 2250 2264 O
’s 2265 2267 O
2018 2268 2272 O
pull-out 2273 2281 O
from 2282 2286 O
the 2287 2290 O
deal 2291 2295 O
and 2296 2299 O
reimposition 2300 2312 O
of 2313 2315 O
tough 2316 2321 O
sanctions 2322 2331 O
that 2332 2336 O
have 2337 2341 O
crippled 2342 2350 O
the 2351 2354 O
Iranian 2355 2362 I-MISC
economy 2363 2370 O
. 2371 2372 O

-DOCSTART- - - O

ANKARA 21 27 I-LOC
( 28 29 O
Reuters 30 37 I-ORG
) 38 39 O
- 40 41 O
Turkey 42 48 I-LOC
has 49 52 O
entered 53 60 O
its 61 64 O
first 65 70 O
full 71 75 O
weekend 76 83 O
lockdown 84 92 O
since 93 98 O
May 99 102 O
after 103 108 O
coronavirus 109 120 O
infections 121 131 O
and 132 135 O
deaths 136 142 O
hit 143 146 O
record 147 153 O
highs 154 159 O
in 160 162 O
recent 163 169 O
days 170 174 O
. 175 176 O

Slideshow 178 187 O
( 188 189 O
5 190 191 O
images 192 198 O
) 199 200 O

The 202 205 O
country 206 213 O
of 214 216 O
83 217 219 O
million 220 227 O
people 228 234 O
on 235 237 O
Friday 238 244 O
recorded 245 253 O
32,736 254 260 O
new 261 264 O
cases 265 270 O
, 271 272 O
including 273 282 O
asymptomatic 283 295 O
ones 296 300 O
, 301 302 O
the 303 306 O
highest 307 314 O
number 315 321 O
since 322 327 O
the 328 331 O
beginning 332 341 O
of 342 344 O
the 345 348 O
pandemic 349 357 O
in 358 360 O
March 361 366 O
. 367 368 O

The 370 373 O
total 374 379 O
death 380 385 O
toll 386 390 O
rose 391 395 O
by 396 398 O
193 399 402 O
on 403 405 O
Friday 406 412 O
, 413 414 O
touching 415 423 O
a 424 425 O
daily 426 431 O
record 432 438 O
level 439 444 O
seen 445 449 O
earlier 450 457 O
this 458 462 O
week 463 467 O
, 468 469 O
to 470 472 O
14,509 473 479 O
. 480 481 O

Turkish 483 490 I-MISC
television 491 501 O
showed 502 508 O
largely 509 516 O
empty 517 522 O
squares 523 530 O
and 531 534 O
streets 535 542 O
on 543 545 O
Saturday 546 554 O
in 555 557 O
the 558 561 O
largest 562 569 O
city 570 574 O
Istanbul 575 583 I-LOC
, 584 585 O
the 586 589 O
capital 590 597 O
Ankara 598 604 I-LOC
and 605 608 O
the 609 612 O
third 613 618 O
largest 619 626 O
city 627 631 O
Izmir 632 637 I-LOC
, 638 639 O
with 640 644 O
only 645 649 O
a 650 651 O
few 652 655 O
people 656 662 O
and 663 666 O
vehicles 667 675 O
out 676 679 O
and 680 683 O
about 684 689 O
. 690 691 O

Interior 693 701 O
Minister 702 710 O
Suleyman 711 719 I-PER
Soylu 720 725 I-PER
was 726 729 O
quoted 730 736 O
as 737 739 O
saying 740 746 O
by 747 749 O
state-owned 750 761 O
Anadolu 762 769 I-ORG
news 770 774 O
agency 775 781 O
that 782 786 O
most 787 791 O
people 792 798 O
were 799 803 O
obeying 804 811 O
the 812 815 O
lockdown 816 824 O
rules 825 830 O
. 831 832 O

Turkey 834 840 I-LOC
now 841 844 O
ranks 845 850 O
fourth 851 857 O
globally 858 866 O
for 867 870 O
the 871 874 O
number 875 881 O
of 882 884 O
daily 885 890 O
new 891 894 O
cases 895 900 O
, 901 902 O
behind 903 909 O
only 910 914 O
the 915 918 O
United 919 925 I-LOC
States 926 932 I-LOC
, 933 934 O
India 935 940 I-LOC
and 941 944 O
Brazil 945 951 I-LOC
- 952 953 O
all 954 957 O
countries 958 967 O
with 968 972 O
far 973 976 O
larger 977 983 O
populations 984 995 O
than 996 1000 O
Turkey 1001 1007 I-LOC
. 1008 1009 O

For 1011 1014 O
four 1015 1019 O
months 1020 1026 O
, 1027 1028 O
Turkey 1029 1035 I-LOC
only 1036 1040 O
reported 1041 1049 O
daily 1050 1055 O
symptomatic 1056 1067 O
cases 1068 1073 O
, 1074 1075 O
but 1076 1079 O
it 1080 1082 O
has 1083 1086 O
reported 1087 1095 O
all 1096 1099 O
cases 1100 1105 O
since 1106 1111 O
Nov. 1112 1116 O
25 1117 1119 O
. 1120 1121 O

Historical 1123 1133 O
data 1134 1138 O
for 1139 1142 O
all 1143 1146 O
positive 1147 1155 O
cases 1156 1161 O
and 1162 1165 O
the 1166 1169 O
cumulative 1170 1180 O
total 1181 1186 O
are 1187 1190 O
still 1191 1196 O
not 1197 1200 O
available 1201 1210 O
. 1211 1212 O

Turkey 1214 1220 I-LOC
last 1221 1225 O
imposed 1226 1233 O
full 1234 1238 O
weekend 1239 1246 O
lockdowns 1247 1256 O
in 1257 1259 O
large 1260 1265 O
cities 1266 1272 O
in 1273 1275 O
May 1276 1279 O
. 1280 1281 O

It 1283 1285 O
announced 1286 1295 O
nationwide 1296 1306 O
weekend 1307 1314 O
curfews 1315 1322 O
last 1323 1327 O
month 1328 1333 O
, 1334 1335 O
but 1336 1339 O
the 1340 1343 O
measures 1344 1352 O
failed 1353 1359 O
to 1360 1362 O
halt 1363 1367 O
the 1368 1371 O
rise 1372 1376 O
in 1377 1379 O
new 1380 1383 O
cases 1384 1389 O
and 1390 1393 O
deaths 1394 1400 O
. 1401 1402 O

President 1404 1413 O
Tayyip 1414 1420 I-PER
Erdogan 1421 1428 I-PER
announced 1429 1438 O
the 1439 1442 O
full 1443 1447 O
weekend 1448 1455 O
lockdown 1456 1464 O
on 1465 1467 O
Monday 1468 1474 O
, 1475 1476 O
as 1477 1479 O
well 1480 1484 O
as 1485 1487 O
a 1488 1489 O
curfew 1490 1496 O
on 1497 1499 O
weekdays 1500 1508 O
. 1509 1510 O

He 1512 1514 O
said 1515 1519 O
measures 1520 1528 O
against 1529 1536 O
the 1537 1540 O
coronavirus 1541 1552 O
were 1553 1557 O
being 1558 1563 O
taken 1564 1569 O
carefully 1570 1579 O
to 1580 1582 O
minimise 1583 1591 O
the 1592 1595 O
impact 1596 1602 O
on 1603 1605 O
the 1606 1609 O
economy 1610 1617 O
. 1618 1619 O

The 1621 1624 O
lockdown 1625 1633 O
and 1634 1637 O
curfews 1638 1645 O
exclude 1646 1653 O
some 1654 1658 O
sectors 1659 1666 O
, 1667 1668 O
including 1669 1678 O
supply 1679 1685 O
chains 1686 1692 O
and 1693 1696 O
production 1697 1707 O
. 1708 1709 O

Turkey 1711 1717 I-LOC
’s 1718 1720 O
economy 1721 1728 O
contracted 1729 1739 O
9.9 1740 1743 O
% 1744 1745 O
year-on-year 1746 1758 O
in 1759 1761 O
the 1762 1765 O
second 1766 1772 O
quarter 1773 1780 O
due 1781 1784 O
to 1785 1787 O
the 1788 1791 O
coronavirus 1792 1803 O
restrictions 1804 1816 O
. 1817 1818 O

It 1820 1822 O
rebounded 1823 1832 O
in 1833 1835 O
the 1836 1839 O
third 1840 1845 O
quarter 1846 1853 O
, 1854 1855 O
growing 1856 1863 O
6.7 1864 1867 O
% 1868 1869 O
after 1870 1875 O
the 1876 1879 O
restrictions 1880 1892 O
were 1893 1897 O
lifted 1898 1904 O
. 1905 1906 O

Economists 1908 1918 O
expect 1919 1925 O
the 1926 1929 O
new 1930 1933 O
measures 1934 1942 O
to 1943 1945 O
have 1946 1950 O
a 1951 1952 O
lesser 1953 1959 O
impact 1960 1966 O
on 1967 1969 O
growth 1970 1976 O
in 1977 1979 O
the 1980 1983 O
final 1984 1989 O
quarter 1990 1997 O
than 1998 2002 O
they 2003 2007 O
did 2008 2011 O
in 2012 2014 O
the 2015 2018 O
second 2019 2025 O
. 2026 2027 O

-DOCSTART- - - O

BEIJING 21 28 I-LOC
, 29 30 O
Dec 31 34 O
7 35 36 O
( 37 38 O
Reuters 39 46 I-ORG
) 47 48 O
- 49 50 O
China 51 56 I-LOC
’s 57 59 O
soybean 60 67 O
imports 68 75 O
in 76 78 O
November 79 87 O
jumped 88 94 O
from 95 99 O
the 100 103 O
previous 104 112 O
year 113 117 O
, 118 119 O
customs 120 127 O
data 128 132 O
showed 133 139 O
on 140 142 O
Monday 143 149 O
, 150 151 O
as 152 154 O
cargoes 155 162 O
booked 163 169 O
from 170 174 O
the 175 178 O
U.S. 179 183 I-LOC
following 184 193 O
the 194 197 O
Phase 198 203 O
1 204 205 O
trade 206 211 O
deal 212 216 O
cleared 217 224 O
customs 225 232 O
. 233 234 O

China 236 241 I-LOC
, 242 243 O
the 244 247 O
world 248 253 O
’s 254 256 O
top 257 260 O
soybean 261 268 O
buyer 269 274 O
, 275 276 O
brought 277 284 O
in 285 287 O
9.59 288 292 O
million 293 300 O
tonnes 301 307 O
, 308 309 O
up 310 312 O
from 313 317 O
8.28 318 322 O
million 323 330 O
tonnes 331 337 O
in 338 340 O
the 341 344 O
previous 345 353 O
year 354 358 O
, 359 360 O
data 361 365 O
from 366 370 O
the 371 374 O
General 375 382 I-ORG
Administration 383 397 I-ORG
of 398 400 I-ORG
Customs 401 408 I-ORG
showed 409 415 O
, 416 417 O
as 418 420 O
more 421 425 O
American 426 434 I-MISC
cargoes 435 442 O
arrived 443 450 O
in 451 453 O
the 454 457 O
fourth 458 464 O
quarter 465 472 O
. 473 474 O

Chinese 476 483 I-MISC
buyers 484 490 O
stepped 491 498 O
up 499 501 O
purchases 502 511 O
of 512 514 O
U.S. 515 519 I-LOC
farm 520 524 O
produce 525 532 O
including 533 542 O
soybeans 543 551 O
to 552 554 O
fulfill 555 562 O
China 563 568 I-LOC
’s 569 571 O
pledge 572 578 O
in 579 581 O
the 582 585 O
initial 586 593 O
trade 594 599 O
deal 600 604 O
it 605 607 O
signed 608 614 O
with 615 619 O
the 620 623 O
United 624 630 I-LOC
States 631 637 I-LOC
in 638 640 O
January 641 648 O
this 649 653 O
year 654 658 O
. 659 660 O

( 662 663 O
Reporting 664 673 O
by 674 676 O
Hallie 677 683 I-PER
Gu 684 686 I-PER
and 687 690 O
Dominique 691 700 I-PER
Patton 701 707 I-PER
; 708 709 O
Editing 710 717 O
by 718 720 O
Kim 721 724 I-PER
Coghill 725 732 I-PER
) 733 734 O

-DOCSTART- - - O

FILE 21 25 O
PHOTO 26 31 O
: 32 33 O
Flags 34 39 O
of 40 42 O
U.S. 43 47 I-LOC
and 48 51 O
China 52 57 I-LOC
are 58 61 O
displayed 62 71 O
at 72 74 O
American 75 83 I-ORG
International 84 97 I-ORG
Chamber 98 105 I-ORG
of 106 108 I-ORG
Commerce 109 117 I-ORG
( 118 119 O
AICC 120 124 I-ORG
) 125 126 O
's 127 129 O
booth 130 135 O
during 136 142 O
China 143 148 I-MISC
International 149 162 I-MISC
Fair 163 167 I-MISC
for 168 171 I-MISC
Trade 172 177 I-MISC
in 178 180 I-MISC
Services 181 189 I-MISC
in 190 192 O
Beijing 193 200 I-LOC
, 201 202 O
China 203 208 I-LOC
, 209 210 O
May 211 214 O
28 215 217 O
, 218 219 O
2019 220 224 O
. 225 226 O

REUTERS 228 235 I-ORG
/ 236 237 O
Jason 238 243 I-PER
Lee 244 247 I-PER

BEIJING 249 256 I-LOC
( 257 258 O
Reuters 259 266 I-ORG
) 267 268 O
- 269 270 O
China 271 276 I-LOC
said 277 281 O
on 282 284 O
Monday 285 291 O
it 292 294 O
firmly 295 301 O
opposes 302 309 O
and 310 313 O
strongly 314 322 O
condemns 323 331 O
U.S. 332 336 I-LOC
interference 337 349 O
in 350 352 O
its 353 356 O
domestic 357 365 O
affairs 366 373 O
if 374 376 O
a 377 378 O
media 379 384 O
report 385 391 O
that 392 396 O
Washington 397 407 I-LOC
is 408 410 O
preparing 411 420 O
new 421 424 O
sanctions 425 434 O
on 435 437 O
Chinese 438 445 I-MISC
officials 446 455 O
over 456 460 O
a 461 462 O
Hong 463 467 I-LOC
Kong 468 472 I-LOC
crackdown 473 482 O
is 483 485 O
true 486 490 O
. 491 492 O

If 494 496 O
the 497 500 O
United 501 507 I-LOC
States 508 514 I-LOC
insists 515 522 O
on 523 525 O
going 526 531 O
down 532 536 O
the 537 540 O
wrong 541 546 O
path 547 551 O
, 552 553 O
China 554 559 I-LOC
will 560 564 O
continue 565 573 O
to 574 576 O
take 577 581 O
firm 582 586 O
counter 587 594 O
measures 595 603 O
to 604 606 O
safeguard 607 616 O
its 617 620 O
sovereignty 621 632 O
and 633 636 O
security 637 645 O
, 646 647 O
Hua 648 651 I-PER
Chunying 652 660 I-PER
, 661 662 O
a 663 664 O
spokeswoman 665 676 O
with 677 681 O
the 682 685 O
foreign 686 693 O
ministry 694 702 O
told 703 707 O
a 708 709 O
briefing 710 718 O
. 719 720 O

The 722 725 O
United 726 732 I-LOC
States 733 739 I-LOC
is 740 742 O
preparing 743 752 O
to 753 755 O
impose 756 762 O
sanctions 763 772 O
on 773 775 O
at 776 778 O
least 779 784 O
a 785 786 O
dozen 787 792 O
Chinese 793 800 I-MISC
officials 801 810 O
over 811 815 O
their 816 821 O
alleged 822 829 O
role 830 834 O
in 835 837 O
Beijing 838 845 I-LOC
’s 846 848 O
disqualification 849 865 O
of 866 868 O
elected 869 876 O
opposition 877 887 O
legislators 888 899 O
in 900 902 O
Hong 903 907 I-LOC
Kong 908 912 I-LOC
, 913 914 O
Reuters 915 922 I-ORG
reported 923 931 O
on 932 934 O
Monday 935 941 O
citing 942 948 O
sources 949 956 O
. 957 958 O

-DOCSTART- - - O

LONDON 21 27 I-LOC
/ 28 29 O
BRUSSELS 30 38 I-LOC
( 39 40 O
Reuters 41 48 I-ORG
) 49 50 O
- 51 52 O
Post-Brexit 53 64 I-MISC
trade 65 70 O
talks 71 76 O
hung 77 81 O
in 82 84 O
the 85 88 O
balance 89 96 O
on 97 99 O
Monday 100 106 O
as 107 109 O
Britain 110 117 I-LOC
and 118 121 O
the 122 125 O
European 126 134 I-ORG
Union 135 140 I-ORG
made 141 145 O
a 146 147 O
last-ditch 148 158 O
attempt 159 166 O
to 167 169 O
bridge 170 176 O
significant 177 188 O
differences 189 200 O
and 201 204 O
reach 205 210 O
a 211 212 O
deal 213 217 O
that 218 222 O
would 223 228 O
avoid 229 234 O
a 235 236 O
disorderly 237 247 O
exit 248 252 O
in 253 255 O
just 256 260 O
24 261 263 O
days 264 268 O
. 269 270 O

EU 272 274 I-ORG
chief 275 280 O
Brexit 281 287 I-MISC
negotiator 288 298 O
Michel 299 305 I-PER
Barnier 306 313 I-PER
takes 314 319 O
part 320 324 O
in 325 327 O
a 328 329 O
meeting 330 337 O
of 338 340 O
ambassadors 341 352 O
of 353 355 O
European 356 364 I-ORG
Union 365 370 I-ORG
governments 371 382 O
in 383 385 O
Brussels 386 394 I-LOC
, 395 396 O
Belgium 397 404 I-LOC
December 405 413 O
7 414 415 O
, 416 417 O
2020 418 422 O
. 423 424 O

John 426 430 I-PER
Thys 431 435 I-PER
/ 436 437 O
Pool 438 442 I-ORG
via 443 446 O
REUTERS 447 454 I-ORG

Irish 732 737 I-MISC
Prime 738 743 O
Minister 744 752 O
Micheal 753 760 I-PER
Martin 761 767 I-PER
said 768 772 O
on 773 775 O
Sunday 776 782 O
the 783 786 O
chances 787 794 O
of 795 797 O
a 798 799 O
deal 800 804 O
were 805 809 O
50-50 810 815 O
. 816 817 O

Investment 819 829 O
bank 830 834 O
JPMorgan 835 843 I-ORG
said 844 848 O
odds 849 853 O
of 854 856 O
a 857 858 O
no-trade 859 867 O
deal 868 872 O
exit 873 877 O
had 878 881 O
risen 882 887 O
to 888 890 O
one 891 894 O
third 895 900 O
from 901 905 O
20 906 908 O
% 909 910 O
. 911 912 O

EU 914 916 I-ORG
chief 917 922 O
negotiator 923 933 O
Michel 934 940 I-PER
Barnier 941 948 I-PER
was 949 952 O
“ 953 954 O
rather 955 961 O
downbeat 962 970 O
as 971 973 O
to 974 976 O
the 977 980 O
prospects 981 990 O
of 991 993 O
agreement 994 1003 O
” 1004 1005 O
when 1006 1010 O
he 1011 1013 O
spoke 1014 1019 O
to 1020 1022 O
national 1023 1031 O
envoys 1032 1038 O
in 1039 1041 O
Brussels 1042 1050 I-LOC
on 1051 1053 O
Monday 1054 1060 O
morning 1061 1068 O
, 1069 1070 O
according 1071 1080 O
to 1081 1083 O
one 1084 1087 O
diplomat 1088 1096 O
, 1097 1098 O
adding 1099 1105 O
that 1106 1110 O
Johnson 1111 1118 I-PER
would 1119 1124 O
have 1125 1129 O
to 1130 1132 O
make 1133 1137 O
the 1138 1141 O
ultimate 1142 1150 O
call 1151 1155 O
on 1156 1158 O
a 1159 1160 O
deal 1161 1165 O
. 1166 1167 O

“ 1169 1170 O
The 1171 1174 O
ball 1175 1179 O
is 1180 1182 O
in 1183 1185 O
BoJo 1186 1190 I-PER
’s 1191 1193 O
( 1194 1195 O
Johnson 1196 1203 I-PER
’s 1204 1206 O
) 1207 1208 O
court 1209 1214 O
, 1215 1216 O
” 1217 1218 O
said 1219 1223 O
the 1224 1227 O
diplomat 1228 1236 O
, 1237 1238 O
who 1239 1242 O
was 1243 1246 O
taking 1247 1253 O
part 1254 1258 O
in 1259 1261 O
the 1262 1265 O
briefing 1266 1274 O
. 1275 1276 O
“ 1277 1278 O

Differences 1280 1291 O
persist 1292 1299 O
on 1300 1302 O
all 1303 1306 O
three 1307 1312 O
issues 1313 1319 O
. 1320 1321 O
” 1322 1323 O

Britain 1325 1332 I-LOC
formally 1333 1341 O
left 1342 1346 O
the 1347 1350 O
EU 1351 1353 I-ORG
on 1354 1356 O
Jan. 1357 1361 O
31 1362 1364 O
but 1365 1368 O
has 1369 1372 O
been 1373 1377 O
in 1378 1380 O
a 1381 1382 O
transition 1383 1393 O
period 1394 1400 O
since 1401 1406 O
then 1407 1411 O
under 1412 1417 O
which 1418 1423 O
rules 1424 1429 O
on 1430 1432 O
trade 1433 1438 O
, 1439 1440 O
travel 1441 1447 O
and 1448 1451 O
business 1452 1460 O
remain 1461 1467 O
unchanged 1468 1477 O
. 1478 1479 O

For 1481 1484 O
weeks 1485 1490 O
, 1491 1492 O
the 1493 1496 O
two 1497 1500 O
sides 1501 1506 O
have 1507 1511 O
been 1512 1516 O
haggling 1517 1525 O
- 1526 1527 O
as 1528 1530 O
yet 1531 1534 O
without 1535 1542 O
a 1543 1544 O
result 1545 1551 O
- 1552 1553 O
over 1554 1558 O
fishing 1559 1566 O
rights 1567 1573 O
in 1574 1576 O
British 1577 1584 I-MISC
waters 1585 1591 O
, 1592 1593 O
ensuring 1594 1602 O
fair 1603 1607 O
competition 1608 1619 O
for 1620 1623 O
companies 1624 1633 O
and 1634 1637 O
ways 1638 1642 O
to 1643 1645 O
solve 1646 1651 O
future 1652 1658 O
disputes 1659 1667 O
. 1668 1669 O

In 1671 1673 O
Brussels 1674 1682 I-LOC
, 1683 1684 O
an 1685 1687 O
EU 1688 1690 I-ORG
diplomat 1691 1699 O
told 1700 1704 O
Reuters 1705 1712 I-ORG
that 1713 1717 O
Britain 1718 1725 I-LOC
had 1726 1729 O
failed 1730 1736 O
to 1737 1739 O
make 1740 1744 O
the 1745 1748 O
“ 1749 1750 O
necessary 1751 1760 O
choices 1761 1768 O
” 1769 1770 O
on 1771 1773 O
fishing 1774 1781 O
and 1782 1785 O
fair 1786 1790 O
competition 1791 1802 O
to 1803 1805 O
make 1806 1810 O
a 1811 1812 O
deal 1813 1817 O
possible 1818 1826 O
on 1827 1829 O
trade 1830 1835 O
- 1836 1837 O
worth 1838 1843 O
nearly 1844 1850 O
$ 1851 1852 O
1 1853 1854 O
trillion 1855 1863 O
each 1864 1868 O
year 1869 1873 O
. 1874 1875 O

In 1877 1879 O
London 1880 1886 I-LOC
, 1887 1888 O
a 1889 1890 O
British 1891 1898 I-MISC
lawmaker 1899 1907 O
in 1908 1910 O
Johnson 1911 1918 I-PER
’s 1919 1921 O
ruling 1922 1928 O
Conservative 1929 1941 I-ORG
Party 1942 1947 I-ORG
said 1948 1952 O
France 1953 1959 I-LOC
would 1960 1965 O
have 1966 1970 O
to 1971 1973 O
make 1974 1978 O
concessions 1979 1990 O
on 1991 1993 O
fishing 1994 2001 O
and 2002 2005 O
the 2006 2009 O
EU 2010 2012 I-ORG
would 2013 2018 O
have 2019 2023 O
to 2024 2026 O
drop 2027 2031 O
their 2032 2037 O
demands 2038 2045 O
on 2046 2048 O
the 2049 2052 O
level 2053 2058 O
playing 2059 2066 O
field 2067 2072 O
. 2073 2074 O

NO 2076 2078 O
DEAL 2079 2083 O
? 2084 2085 O

Failure 2087 2094 O
to 2095 2097 O
secure 2098 2104 O
a 2105 2106 O
deal 2107 2111 O
would 2112 2117 O
clog 2118 2122 O
borders 2123 2130 O
, 2131 2132 O
upset 2133 2138 O
financial 2139 2148 O
markets 2149 2156 O
and 2157 2160 O
disrupt 2161 2168 O
delicate 2169 2177 O
supply 2178 2184 O
chains 2185 2191 O
across 2192 2198 O
Europe 2199 2205 I-LOC
and 2206 2209 O
beyond 2210 2216 O
as 2217 2219 O
the 2220 2223 O
world 2224 2229 O
tries 2230 2235 O
to 2236 2238 O
cope 2239 2243 O
with 2244 2248 O
the 2249 2252 O
vast 2253 2257 O
economic 2258 2266 O
cost 2267 2271 O
of 2272 2274 O
the 2275 2278 O
COVID-19 2279 2287 I-MISC
pandemic 2288 2296 O
. 2297 2298 O

Sterling 2300 2308 O
fell 2309 2313 O
0.7 2314 2317 O
% 2318 2319 O
against 2320 2327 O
the 2328 2331 O
dollar 2332 2338 O
to 2339 2341 O
$ 2342 2343 O
1.3344 2344 2350 O
, 2351 2352 O
down 2353 2357 O
from 2358 2362 O
the 2363 2366 O
2-1 2367 2370 O
/ 2371 2372 O
2-year 2373 2379 O
highs 2380 2385 O
of 2386 2388 O
$ 2389 2390 O
1.3540 2391 2397 O
hit 2398 2401 O
on 2402 2404 O
Friday 2405 2411 O
. 2412 2413 O

Measures 2415 2423 O
of 2424 2426 O
expected 2427 2435 O
swings 2436 2442 O
in 2443 2445 O
the 2446 2449 O
British 2450 2457 I-MISC
pound 2458 2463 O
jumped 2464 2470 O
to 2471 2473 O
eight-month 2474 2485 O
highs 2486 2491 O
. 2492 2493 O

With 2495 2499 O
just 2500 2504 O
days 2505 2509 O
left 2510 2514 O
for 2515 2518 O
a 2519 2520 O
deal 2521 2525 O
to 2526 2528 O
be 2529 2531 O
agreed 2532 2538 O
, 2539 2540 O
EU 2541 2543 I-ORG
diplomats 2544 2553 O
said 2554 2558 O
it 2559 2561 O
a 2562 2563 O
decisive 2564 2572 O
moment 2573 2579 O
for 2580 2583 O
both 2584 2588 O
the 2589 2592 O
United 2593 2599 I-LOC
Kingdom 2600 2607 I-LOC
and 2608 2611 O
the 2612 2615 O
bloc 2616 2620 O
which 2621 2626 O
built 2627 2632 O
the 2633 2636 O
ruined 2637 2643 O
nations 2644 2651 O
of 2652 2654 O
Europe 2655 2661 I-LOC
into 2662 2666 O
a 2667 2668 O
global 2669 2675 O
power 2676 2681 O
after 2682 2687 O
the 2688 2691 O
devastation 2692 2703 O
of 2704 2706 O
World 2707 2712 I-MISC
War 2713 2716 I-MISC
Two 2717 2720 I-MISC
. 2721 2722 O

“ 2724 2725 O
Decisive 2726 2734 O
hours 2735 2740 O
for 2741 2744 O
the 2745 2748 O
future 2749 2755 O
of 2756 2758 O
EU-UK 2759 2764 I-MISC
relations 2765 2774 O
, 2775 2776 O
” 2777 2778 O
said 2779 2783 O
Sebastian 2784 2793 I-PER
Fischer 2794 2801 I-PER
, 2802 2803 O
an 2804 2806 O
EU 2807 2809 I-ORG
spokesman 2810 2819 O
for 2820 2823 O
Germany 2824 2831 I-LOC
, 2832 2833 O
the 2834 2837 O
current 2838 2845 O
holder 2846 2852 O
of 2853 2855 O
the 2856 2859 O
EU 2860 2862 I-ORG
presidency 2863 2873 O
. 2874 2875 O

While 2877 2882 O
some 2883 2887 O
diplomats 2888 2897 O
said 2898 2902 O
the 2903 2906 O
last-minute 2907 2918 O
drama 2919 2924 O
showed 2925 2931 O
a 2932 2933 O
deal 2934 2938 O
was 2939 2942 O
close 2943 2948 O
, 2949 2950 O
Ireland 2951 2958 I-LOC
- 2959 2960 O
the 2961 2964 O
EU 2965 2967 I-ORG
member 2968 2974 O
state 2975 2980 O
whose 2981 2986 O
economy 2987 2994 O
is 2995 2997 O
likely 2998 3004 O
to 3005 3007 O
be 3008 3010 O
worst 3011 3016 O
hit 3017 3020 O
by 3021 3023 O
a 3024 3025 O
disorderly 3026 3036 O
Brexit 3037 3043 I-MISC
- 3044 3045 O
said 3046 3050 O
it 3051 3053 O
would 3054 3059 O
not 3060 3063 O
be 3064 3066 O
shocked 3067 3074 O
if 3075 3077 O
talks 3078 3083 O
fell 3084 3088 O
apart 3089 3094 O
. 3095 3096 O

“ 3098 3099 O
I 3100 3101 O
still 3102 3107 O
think 3108 3113 O
it 3114 3116 O
is 3117 3119 O
more 3120 3124 O
likely 3125 3131 O
than 3132 3136 O
not 3137 3140 O
that 3141 3145 O
we 3146 3148 O
will 3149 3153 O
find 3154 3158 O
a 3159 3160 O
way 3161 3164 O
of 3165 3167 O
getting 3168 3175 O
a 3176 3177 O
deal 3178 3182 O
done 3183 3187 O
but 3188 3191 O
I 3192 3193 O
wo 3194 3196 O
n’t 3197 3200 O
be 3201 3203 O
shocked 3204 3211 O
if 3212 3214 O
it 3215 3217 O
falls 3218 3223 O
apart 3224 3229 O
, 3230 3231 O
” 3232 3233 O
Irish 3234 3239 I-MISC
Foreign 3240 3247 O
Minister 3248 3256 O
Simon 3257 3262 I-PER
Coveney 3263 3270 I-PER
was 3271 3274 O
quoted 3275 3281 O
as 3282 3284 O
saying 3285 3291 O
by 3292 3294 O
the 3295 3298 O
Irish 3299 3304 I-ORG
Times 3305 3310 I-ORG
. 3311 3312 O

“ 3314 3315 O
If 3316 3318 O
we 3319 3321 O
do 3322 3324 O
n’t 3325 3328 O
get 3329 3332 O
a 3333 3334 O
deal 3335 3339 O
in 3340 3342 O
the 3343 3346 O
next 3347 3351 O
few 3352 3355 O
days 3356 3360 O
, 3361 3362 O
then 3363 3367 O
obviously 3368 3377 O
there 3378 3383 O
are 3384 3387 O
serious 3388 3395 O
problems 3396 3404 O
around 3405 3411 O
ratification 3412 3424 O
and 3425 3428 O
timelines 3429 3438 O
. 3439 3440 O
” 3441 3442 O

In 3444 3446 O
a 3447 3448 O
move 3449 3453 O
that 3454 3458 O
could 3459 3464 O
further 3465 3472 O
undermine 3473 3482 O
the 3483 3486 O
talks 3487 3492 O
, 3493 3494 O
the 3495 3498 O
British 3499 3506 I-MISC
government 3507 3517 O
will 3518 3522 O
press 3523 3528 O
ahead 3529 3534 O
with 3535 3539 O
draft 3540 3545 O
laws 3546 3550 O
this 3551 3555 O
week 3556 3560 O
that 3561 3565 O
would 3566 3571 O
breach 3572 3578 O
London 3579 3585 I-LOC
’s 3586 3588 O
earlier 3589 3596 O
divorce 3597 3604 O
treaty 3605 3611 O
with 3612 3616 O
the 3617 3620 O
bloc 3621 3625 O
. 3626 3627 O

Junior 3629 3635 O
Foreign 3636 3643 I-ORG
Office 3644 3650 I-ORG
Minister 3651 3659 O
James 3660 3665 I-PER
Cleverly 3666 3674 I-PER
said 3675 3679 O
on 3680 3682 O
Monday 3683 3689 O
the 3690 3693 O
clauses 3694 3701 O
that 3702 3706 O
breach 3707 3713 O
the 3714 3717 O
treaty 3718 3724 O
would 3725 3730 O
be 3731 3733 O
re-inserted 3734 3745 O
. 3746 3747 O

-DOCSTART- - - O

FILE 21 25 O
PHOTO 26 31 O
: 32 33 O
People 34 40 O
walk 41 45 O
down 46 50 O
a 51 52 O
city 53 57 O
laneway 58 65 O
after 66 71 O
coronavirus 72 83 O
disease 84 91 O
( 92 93 O
COVID-19 94 102 I-MISC
) 103 104 O
restrictions 105 117 O
were 118 122 O
eased 123 128 O
for 129 132 O
the 133 136 O
state 137 142 O
of 143 145 O
Victoria 146 154 I-LOC
, 155 156 O
in 157 159 O
Melbourne 160 169 I-LOC
, 170 171 O
Australia 172 181 I-LOC
, 182 183 O
October 184 191 O
28 192 194 O
, 195 196 O
2020 197 201 O
. 202 203 O

REUTERS 205 212 I-ORG
/ 213 214 O
Sandra 215 221 I-PER
Sanders 222 229 I-PER

MELBOURNE 231 240 I-LOC
( 241 242 O
Reuters 243 250 I-ORG
) 251 252 O
- 253 254 O
Australia 255 264 I-LOC
’s 265 267 O
Victoria 268 276 I-LOC
state 277 282 O
eased 283 288 O
COVID-19 289 297 I-MISC
restrictions 298 310 O
on 311 313 O
Sunday 314 320 O
after 321 326 O
the 327 330 O
country 331 338 O
’s 339 341 O
pandemic 342 350 O
hotspot 351 358 O
recorded 359 367 O
37 368 370 O
days 371 375 O
without 376 383 O
any 384 387 O
new 388 391 O
coronavirus 392 403 O
infections 404 414 O
, 415 416 O
moving 417 423 O
toward 424 430 O
a 431 432 O
“ 433 434 O
COVID-safe 435 445 I-MISC
” 446 447 O
holiday 448 455 O
season 456 462 O
. 463 464 O

From 466 470 O
midnight 471 479 O
on 480 482 O
Sunday 483 489 O
, 490 491 O
up 492 494 O
to 495 497 O
100 498 501 O
people 502 508 O
will 509 513 O
be 514 516 O
able 517 521 O
to 522 524 O
attend 525 531 O
public 532 538 O
gatherings 539 549 O
such 550 554 O
as 555 557 O
weddings 558 566 O
, 567 568 O
with 569 573 O
density 574 581 O
rules 582 587 O
of 588 590 O
one 591 594 O
person 595 601 O
per 602 605 O
two 606 609 O
square 610 616 O
metres 617 623 O
remaining 624 633 O
in 634 636 O
place 637 642 O
, 643 644 O
while 645 650 O
50 651 653 O
% 654 655 O
of 656 658 O
office 659 665 O
workers 666 673 O
will 674 678 O
be 679 681 O
able 682 686 O
to 687 689 O
return 690 696 O
to 697 699 O
workplaces 700 710 O
by 711 713 O
Jan. 714 718 O
11 719 721 O
, 722 723 O
up 724 726 O
from 727 731 O
25 732 734 O
% 735 736 O
now 737 740 O
, 741 742 O
the 743 746 O
state 747 752 O
’s 753 755 O
premier 756 763 O
said 764 768 O
. 769 770 O

“ 772 773 O
Today 774 779 O
we 780 782 O
can 783 786 O
take 787 791 O
some 792 796 O
big 797 800 O
steps 801 806 O
, 807 808 O
not 809 812 O
to 813 815 O
normal 816 822 O
, 823 824 O
but 825 828 O
to 829 831 O
a 832 833 O
COVID-safe 834 844 I-MISC
summer 845 851 O
( 852 853 O
but 854 857 O
) 858 859 O
we 860 862 O
all 863 866 O
need 867 871 O
to 872 874 O
remain 875 881 O
vigilant 882 890 O
and 891 894 O
we 895 897 O
all 898 901 O
need 902 906 O
to 907 909 O
play 910 914 O
our 915 918 O
part 919 923 O
, 924 925 O
” 926 927 O
Premier 928 935 O
Daniel 936 942 I-PER
Andrews 943 950 I-PER
told 951 955 O
a 956 957 O
news 958 962 O
conference 963 973 O
. 974 975 O

Masks 977 982 O
will 983 987 O
remain 988 994 O
mandatory 995 1004 O
at 1005 1007 O
indoor 1008 1014 O
venues 1015 1021 O
and 1022 1025 O
on 1026 1028 O
public 1029 1035 O
and 1036 1039 O
ride-share 1040 1050 O
transport 1051 1060 O
, 1061 1062 O
he 1063 1065 O
said 1066 1070 O
. 1071 1072 O

Public 1074 1080 O
health 1081 1087 O
concerns 1088 1096 O
eased 1097 1102 O
after 1103 1108 O
two 1109 1112 O
travellers 1113 1123 O
who 1124 1127 O
returned 1128 1136 O
from 1137 1141 O
Germany 1142 1149 I-LOC
, 1150 1151 O
bypassing 1152 1161 O
quarantine 1162 1172 O
in 1173 1175 O
Sydney 1176 1182 I-LOC
to 1183 1185 O
travel 1186 1192 O
straight 1193 1201 O
to 1202 1204 O
Melbourne 1205 1214 I-LOC
, 1215 1216 O
returned 1217 1225 O
negative 1226 1234 O
COVID-19 1235 1243 I-MISC
tests 1244 1249 O
. 1250 1251 O

All 1253 1256 O
passengers 1257 1267 O
on 1268 1270 O
the 1271 1274 O
Saturday 1275 1283 O
afternoon 1284 1293 O
domestic 1294 1302 O
flight 1303 1309 O
between 1310 1317 O
the 1318 1321 O
two 1322 1325 O
cities 1326 1332 O
and 1333 1336 O
some 1337 1341 O
airport 1342 1349 O
staff 1350 1355 O
must 1356 1360 O
remain 1361 1367 O
in 1368 1370 O
self-quarantine 1371 1386 O
until 1387 1392 O
the 1393 1396 O
results 1397 1404 O
from 1405 1409 O
a 1410 1411 O
second 1412 1418 O
test 1419 1423 O
arrive 1424 1430 O
on 1431 1433 O
Monday 1434 1440 O
, 1441 1442 O
a 1443 1444 O
health 1445 1451 O
official 1452 1460 O
said 1461 1465 O
. 1466 1467 O

Australia 1469 1478 I-LOC
recorded 1479 1487 O
7 1488 1489 O
new 1490 1493 O
cases 1494 1499 O
overnight 1500 1509 O
, 1510 1511 O
all 1512 1515 O
returned 1516 1524 O
travellers 1525 1535 O
. 1536 1537 O

The 1539 1542 O
country 1543 1550 O
has 1551 1554 O
all 1555 1558 O
but 1559 1562 O
stamped 1563 1570 O
out 1571 1574 O
the 1575 1578 O
coronavirus 1579 1590 O
through 1591 1598 O
strict 1599 1605 O
quarantine 1606 1616 O
measures 1617 1625 O
, 1626 1627 O
particularly 1628 1640 O
in 1641 1643 O
Victoria 1644 1652 I-LOC
, 1653 1654 O
the 1655 1658 O
second-most 1659 1670 O
populous 1671 1679 O
state 1680 1685 O
, 1686 1687 O
which 1688 1693 O
in 1694 1696 O
early 1697 1702 O
August 1703 1709 O
logged 1710 1716 O
as 1717 1719 O
many 1720 1724 O
as 1725 1727 O
700 1728 1731 O
daily 1732 1737 O
infections 1738 1748 O
. 1749 1750 O

This 1752 1756 O
comes 1757 1762 O
as 1763 1765 O
a 1766 1767 O
Reuters 1768 1775 I-ORG
tally 1776 1781 O
of 1782 1784 O
global 1785 1791 O
infections 1792 1802 O
rose 1803 1807 O
above 1808 1813 O
65.58 1814 1819 O
million 1820 1827 O
people 1828 1834 O
, 1835 1836 O
while 1837 1842 O
more 1843 1847 O
than 1848 1852 O
1.5 1853 1856 O
million 1857 1864 O
people 1865 1871 O
have 1872 1876 O
died 1877 1881 O
, 1882 1883 O
and 1884 1887 O
as 1888 1890 O
the 1891 1894 O
United 1895 1901 I-LOC
States 1902 1908 I-LOC
continues 1909 1918 O
to 1919 1921 O
set 1922 1925 O
single-day 1926 1936 O
records 1937 1944 O
for 1945 1948 O
new 1949 1952 O
infections 1953 1963 O
. 1964 1965 O

-DOCSTART- - - O

( 21 22 O
Reuters 23 30 I-ORG
) 31 32 O
- 33 34 O
Retail 35 41 O
brokerages 42 52 O
Interactive 53 64 I-ORG
Brokers 65 72 I-ORG
Group 73 78 I-ORG
Inc 79 82 I-ORG
and 83 86 O
Robinhood 87 96 I-ORG
experienced 97 108 O
glitches 109 117 O
early 118 123 O
on 124 126 O
Monday 127 133 O
that 134 138 O
prevented 139 148 O
some 149 153 O
or 154 156 O
all 157 160 O
of 161 163 O
their 164 169 O
users 170 175 O
from 176 180 O
trading 181 188 O
as 189 191 O
the 192 195 O
U.S. 196 200 I-LOC
markets 201 208 O
were 209 213 O
opening 214 221 O
. 222 223 O

The 225 228 O
problems 229 237 O
were 238 242 O
the 243 246 O
latest 247 253 O
in 254 256 O
a 257 258 O
string 259 265 O
of 266 268 O
technical 269 278 O
issues 279 285 O
among 286 291 O
retail 292 298 O
brokerages 299 309 O
this 310 314 O
year 315 319 O
as 320 322 O
trading 323 330 O
volumes 331 338 O
have 339 343 O
surged 344 350 O
on 351 353 O
the 354 357 O
back 358 362 O
of 363 365 O
a 366 367 O
move 368 372 O
by 373 375 O
these 376 381 O
brokerages 382 392 O
to 393 395 O
cut 396 399 O
commissions 400 411 O
to 412 414 O
zero 415 419 O
on 420 422 O
most 423 427 O
platforms 428 437 O
, 438 439 O
and 440 443 O
as 444 446 O
markets 447 454 O
surged 455 461 O
this 462 466 O
year 467 471 O
after 472 477 O
a 478 479 O
sharp 480 485 O
downturn 486 494 O
at 495 497 O
the 498 501 O
beginning 502 511 O
of 512 514 O
the 515 518 O
COVID-19 519 527 I-MISC
pandemic 528 536 O
. 537 538 O

Interactive 540 551 I-ORG
Brokers 552 559 I-ORG
said 560 564 O
it 565 567 O
experienced 568 579 O
“ 580 581 O
a 582 583 O
significant 584 595 O
failure 596 603 O
” 604 605 O
in 606 608 O
a 609 610 O
data 611 615 O
storage 616 623 O
system 624 630 O
that 631 635 O
left 636 640 O
its 641 644 O
users 645 650 O
unable 651 657 O
to 658 660 O
trade 661 666 O
, 667 668 O
but 669 672 O
that 673 677 O
most 678 682 O
of 683 685 O
its 686 689 O
services 690 698 O
had 699 702 O
been 703 707 O
restored 708 716 O
and 717 720 O
the 721 724 O
others 725 731 O
were 732 736 O
expected 737 745 O
to 746 748 O
be 749 751 O
up 752 754 O
again 755 760 O
“ 761 762 O
promptly 763 771 O
. 772 773 O
” 774 775 O

“ 777 778 O
We 779 781 O
recognize 782 791 O
the 792 795 O
dislocation 796 807 O
this 808 812 O
has 813 816 O
caused 817 823 O
to 824 826 O
our 827 830 O
clients 831 838 O
, 839 840 O
and 841 844 O
express 845 852 O
our 853 856 O
apologies 857 866 O
, 867 868 O
” 869 870 O
the 871 874 O
New 875 878 I-MISC
York-based 879 889 I-MISC
company 890 897 O
said 898 902 O
in 903 905 O
a 906 907 O
statement 908 917 O
. 918 919 O

The 921 924 O
Menlo 925 930 I-LOC
Park 931 935 I-LOC
, 936 937 O
California-based 938 954 I-MISC
Robinhood 955 964 I-ORG
said 965 969 O
it 970 972 O
experienced 973 984 O
a 985 986 O
“ 987 988 O
disruption 989 999 O
in 1000 1002 O
service 1003 1010 O
, 1011 1012 O
” 1013 1014 O
but 1015 1018 O
that 1019 1023 O
all 1024 1027 O
its 1028 1031 O
systems 1032 1039 O
were 1040 1044 O
now 1045 1048 O
operational 1049 1060 O
. 1061 1062 O

The 1064 1067 O
glitches 1068 1076 O
left 1077 1081 O
users 1082 1087 O
of 1088 1090 O
both 1091 1095 O
brokerages 1096 1106 O
scrambling 1107 1117 O
. 1118 1119 O

“ 1121 1122 O
It 1123 1125 O
is 1126 1128 O
a 1129 1130 O
nightmare 1131 1140 O
holding 1141 1148 O
a 1149 1150 O
position 1151 1159 O
you 1160 1163 O
cannot 1164 1170 O
close 1171 1176 O
at 1177 1179 O
will 1180 1184 O
. 1185 1186 O

It 1188 1190 O
’s 1191 1193 O
like 1194 1198 O
sitting 1199 1206 O
in 1207 1209 O
a 1210 1211 O
car 1212 1215 O
without 1216 1223 O
brakes 1224 1230 O
, 1231 1232 O
” 1233 1234 O
a 1235 1236 O
Berlin-based 1237 1249 I-MISC
Interactive 1250 1261 I-ORG
Brokers 1262 1269 I-ORG
user 1270 1274 O
told 1275 1279 O
Reuters 1280 1287 I-ORG
. 1288 1289 O

“ 1291 1292 O
Please 1293 1299 O
fix 1300 1303 O
the 1304 1307 O
app 1308 1311 O
we 1312 1314 O
ca 1315 1317 O
n’t 1318 1321 O
sell 1322 1326 O
or 1327 1329 O
buy 1330 1333 O
, 1334 1335 O
for 1336 1339 O
options 1340 1347 O
trading 1348 1355 O
it 1356 1358 O
’s 1359 1361 O
killing 1362 1369 O
us 1370 1372 O
every 1373 1378 O
time 1379 1383 O
service 1384 1391 O
is 1392 1394 O
down 1395 1399 O
, 1400 1401 O
” 1402 1403 O
a 1404 1405 O
Robinhood 1406 1415 I-ORG
user 1416 1420 O
said 1421 1425 O
on 1426 1428 O
Twitter 1429 1436 I-MISC
. 1437 1438 O

Retail 1440 1446 O
brokers 1447 1454 O
have 1455 1459 O
been 1460 1464 O
under 1465 1470 O
scrutiny 1471 1479 O
over 1480 1484 O
outages 1485 1492 O
and 1493 1496 O
spent 1497 1502 O
months 1503 1509 O
shoring 1510 1517 O
up 1518 1520 O
their 1521 1526 O
platforms 1527 1536 O
ahead 1537 1542 O
of 1543 1545 O
last 1546 1550 O
month 1551 1556 O
’s 1557 1559 O
U.S. 1560 1564 I-LOC
elections 1565 1574 O
in 1575 1577 O
preparation 1578 1589 O
for 1590 1593 O
expected 1594 1602 O
record 1603 1609 O
volumes 1610 1617 O
, 1618 1619 O
but 1620 1623 O
several 1624 1631 O
high-profile 1632 1644 O
glitches 1645 1653 O
have 1654 1658 O
happened 1659 1667 O
since 1668 1673 O
. 1674 1675 O

“ 1677 1678 O
Obviously 1679 1688 O
, 1689 1690 O
this 1691 1695 O
is 1696 1698 O
a 1699 1700 O
black 1701 1706 O
eye 1707 1710 O
on 1711 1713 O
any 1714 1717 O
firm 1718 1722 O
that 1723 1727 O
has 1728 1731 O
an 1732 1734 O
outage 1735 1741 O
because 1742 1749 O
customers 1750 1759 O
depend 1760 1766 O
upon 1767 1771 O
their 1772 1777 O
access 1778 1784 O
to 1785 1787 O
the 1788 1791 O
market 1792 1798 O
, 1799 1800 O
and 1801 1804 O
the 1805 1808 O
more 1809 1813 O
time-sensitive 1814 1828 O
their 1829 1834 O
trading 1835 1842 O
, 1843 1844 O
the 1845 1848 O
bigger 1849 1855 O
the 1856 1859 O
risk 1860 1864 O
from 1865 1869 O
an 1870 1872 O
outage 1873 1879 O
, 1880 1881 O
” 1882 1883 O
said 1884 1888 O
James 1889 1894 I-PER
Angel 1895 1900 I-PER
, 1901 1902 O
a 1903 1904 O
finance 1905 1912 O
professor 1913 1922 O
at 1923 1925 O
Georgetown 1926 1936 I-ORG
University 1937 1947 I-ORG
. 1948 1949 O

-DOCSTART- - - O

Slideshow 21 30 O
( 31 32 O
5 33 34 O
images 35 41 O
) 42 43 O

LONDON 45 51 I-LOC
( 52 53 O
Reuters 54 61 I-ORG
) 62 63 O
- 64 65 O
Prince 66 72 O
William 73 80 I-PER
and 81 84 O
his 85 88 O
wife 89 93 O
Kate 94 98 I-PER
arrived 99 106 O
in 107 109 O
Edinburgh 110 119 I-LOC
on 120 122 O
Monday 123 129 O
at 130 132 O
the 133 136 O
start 137 142 O
of 143 145 O
a 146 147 O
nationwide 148 158 O
train 159 164 O
tour 165 169 O
of 170 172 O
Britain 173 180 I-LOC
to 181 183 O
meet 184 188 O
and 189 192 O
thank 193 198 O
frontline 199 208 O
workers 209 216 O
, 217 218 O
care 219 223 O
home 224 228 O
staff 229 234 O
and 235 238 O
teachers 239 247 O
for 248 251 O
their 252 257 O
efforts 258 265 O
during 266 272 O
the 273 276 O
COVID-19 277 285 I-MISC
pandemic 286 294 O
. 295 296 O

William 298 305 I-PER
, 306 307 O
Queen 308 313 O
Elizabeth 314 323 I-PER
’s 324 326 O
grandson 327 335 O
and 336 339 O
second-in-line 340 354 O
to 355 357 O
the 358 361 O
throne 362 368 O
, 369 370 O
and 371 374 O
Kate 375 379 I-PER
are 380 383 O
travelling 384 394 O
1,250 395 400 O
miles 401 406 O
across 407 413 O
England 414 421 I-LOC
, 422 423 O
Scotland 424 432 I-LOC
and 433 436 O
Wales 437 442 I-LOC
on 443 445 O
board 446 451 O
the 452 455 O
Royal 456 461 I-MISC
Train 462 467 I-MISC
as 468 470 O
part 471 475 O
of 476 478 O
their 479 484 O
three-day 485 494 O
trip 495 499 O
. 500 501 O

They 503 507 O
kicked 508 514 O
off 515 518 O
the 519 522 O
tour 523 527 O
at 528 530 O
London 531 537 I-LOC
’s 538 540 O
Euston 541 547 I-LOC
Station 548 555 I-LOC
on 556 558 O
Sunday 559 565 O
evening 566 573 O
where 574 579 O
they 580 584 O
were 585 589 O
serenaded 590 599 O
by 600 602 O
Welsh 603 608 I-MISC
pop 609 612 O
star 613 617 O
Shakin 618 624 I-PER
’ 625 626 I-PER
Stevens 627 634 I-PER
singing 635 642 O
his 643 646 O
1980s 647 652 O
hit 653 656 O
“ 657 658 O
Merry 659 664 I-MISC
Christmas 665 674 I-MISC
Everyone 675 683 I-MISC
” 684 685 O
before 686 692 O
leaving 693 700 O
for 701 704 O
Scotland 705 713 I-LOC
. 714 715 O

“ 717 718 O
Thank 719 724 O
you 725 728 O
to 729 731 O
all 732 735 O
transport 736 745 O
workers 746 753 O
everywhere 754 764 O
for 765 768 O
keeping 769 776 O
the 777 780 O
country 781 788 O
moving 789 795 O
throughout 796 806 O
this 807 811 O
difficult 812 821 O
year 822 826 O
, 827 828 O
” 829 830 O
they 831 835 O
wrote 836 841 O
on 842 844 O
a 845 846 O
train 847 852 O
information 853 864 O
board 865 870 O
before 871 877 O
they 878 882 O
set 883 886 O
off 887 890 O
. 891 892 O

Britain 894 901 I-LOC
has 902 905 O
been 906 910 O
the 911 914 O
hardest 915 922 O
hit 923 926 O
country 927 934 O
in 935 937 O
Europe 938 944 I-LOC
by 945 947 O
COVID-19 948 956 I-MISC
, 957 958 O
with 959 963 O
more 964 968 O
than 969 973 O
60,000 974 980 O
deaths 981 987 O
. 988 989 O

“ 991 992 O
The 993 996 O
Duke 997 1001 O
and 1002 1005 O
Duchess 1006 1013 O
are 1014 1017 O
very 1018 1022 O
much 1023 1027 O
looking 1028 1035 O
forward 1036 1043 O
to 1044 1046 O
shining 1047 1054 O
a 1055 1056 O
spotlight 1057 1066 O
on 1067 1069 O
the 1070 1073 O
incredible 1074 1084 O
work 1085 1089 O
that 1090 1094 O
has 1095 1098 O
been 1099 1103 O
done 1104 1108 O
across 1109 1115 O
the 1116 1119 O
country 1120 1127 O
throughout 1128 1138 O
this 1139 1143 O
difficult 1144 1153 O
year 1154 1158 O
, 1159 1160 O
” 1161 1162 O
Kensington 1163 1173 I-LOC
Palace 1174 1180 I-LOC
said 1181 1185 O
in 1186 1188 O
a 1189 1190 O
statement 1191 1200 O
. 1201 1202 O

Queen 1204 1209 O
Victoria 1210 1218 I-PER
was 1219 1222 O
the 1223 1226 O
first 1227 1232 O
reigning 1233 1241 O
monarch 1242 1249 O
to 1250 1252 O
use 1253 1256 O
the 1257 1260 O
Royal 1261 1266 I-MISC
Train 1267 1272 I-MISC
in 1273 1275 O
1842 1276 1280 O
, 1281 1282 O
to 1283 1285 O
travel 1286 1292 O
from 1293 1297 O
Slough 1298 1304 I-LOC
to 1305 1307 O
London 1308 1314 I-LOC
’s 1315 1317 O
Paddington 1318 1328 I-LOC
station 1329 1336 I-LOC
, 1337 1338 O
although 1339 1347 O
critics 1348 1355 O
have 1356 1360 O
questioned 1361 1371 O
its 1372 1375 O
purpose 1376 1383 O
in 1384 1386 O
recent 1387 1393 O
years 1394 1399 O
, 1400 1401 O
saying 1402 1408 O
it 1409 1411 O
is 1412 1414 O
expensive 1415 1424 O
and 1425 1428 O
little 1429 1435 O
used 1436 1440 O
. 1441 1442 O

-DOCSTART- - - O

FILE 21 25 O
PHOTO 26 31 O
: 32 33 O
European 34 42 I-ORG
Commission 43 53 I-ORG
Vice 54 58 O
President 59 68 O
Maros 69 74 I-PER
Sefcovic 75 83 I-PER
reports 84 91 O
on 92 94 O
last 95 99 O
week 100 104 O
's 105 107 O
European 108 116 I-MISC
summit 117 123 O
during 124 130 O
a 131 132 O
plenary 133 140 O
session 141 148 O
at 149 151 O
the 152 155 O
European 156 164 I-ORG
Parliament 165 175 I-ORG
in 176 178 O
Brussels 179 187 I-LOC
, 188 189 O
Belgium 190 197 I-LOC
October 198 205 O
21 206 208 O
, 209 210 O
2020 211 215 O
. 216 217 O

Olivier 219 226 I-PER
Hoslet 227 233 I-PER
/ 234 235 O
Pool 236 240 I-ORG
via 241 244 O
REUTERS 245 252 I-ORG

BRUSSELS 254 262 I-LOC
( 263 264 O
Reuters 265 272 I-ORG
) 273 274 O
- 275 276 O
EU 277 279 I-ORG
and 280 283 O
UK 284 286 I-LOC
officials 287 296 O
will 297 301 O
meet 302 306 O
on 307 309 O
Monday 310 316 O
in 317 319 O
Brussels 320 328 I-LOC
to 329 331 O
discuss 332 339 O
implementing 340 352 O
their 353 358 O
divorce 359 366 O
Brexit 367 373 I-MISC
deal 374 378 O
for 379 382 O
the 383 386 O
sensitive 387 396 O
Irish 397 402 I-MISC
border 403 409 O
in 410 412 O
time 413 417 O
for 418 421 O
the 422 425 O
start 426 431 O
of 432 434 O
2021 435 439 O
, 440 441 O
a 442 443 O
deputy 444 450 O
head 451 455 O
of 456 458 O
the 459 462 O
bloc 463 467 O
’s 468 470 O
executive 471 480 O
European 481 489 I-ORG
Commission 490 500 I-ORG
said 501 505 O
. 506 507 O

“ 509 510 O
I 511 512 O
will 513 517 O
meet 518 522 O
Michael 523 530 I-PER
Gove 531 535 I-PER
today 536 541 O
in 542 544 O
Brussels 545 553 I-LOC
to 554 556 O
discuss 557 564 O
the 565 568 O
implementation 569 583 O
of 584 586 O
the 587 590 O
Withdrawal 591 601 I-MISC
Agreement 602 611 I-MISC
, 612 613 O
including 614 623 O
the 624 627 O
Protocol 628 636 I-MISC
on 637 639 I-MISC
Ireland 640 647 I-MISC
and 648 651 I-MISC
Northern 652 660 I-MISC
Ireland 661 668 I-MISC
. 669 670 O

We 672 674 O
are 675 678 O
working 679 686 O
hard 687 691 O
to 692 694 O
make 695 699 O
sure 700 704 O
it 705 707 O
is 708 710 O
fully 711 716 O
operational 717 728 O
as 729 731 O
of 732 734 O
1 735 736 O
January 737 744 O
2021 745 749 O
, 750 751 O
” 752 753 O
said 754 758 O
the 759 762 O
Commission 763 773 I-ORG
’s 774 776 O
Maros 777 782 I-PER
Sefcovic 783 791 I-PER
. 792 793 O

The 795 798 O
UK 799 801 I-LOC
’s 802 804 O
draft 805 810 O
Internal 811 819 I-MISC
Market 820 826 I-MISC
Bill 827 831 I-MISC
- 832 833 O
which 834 839 O
would 840 845 O
undercut 846 854 O
bits 855 859 O
of 860 862 O
the 863 866 O
Brexit 867 873 I-MISC
divorce 874 881 O
settlement 882 892 O
- 893 894 O
is 895 897 O
due 898 901 O
back 902 906 O
before 907 913 O
the 914 917 O
parliament 918 928 O
late 929 933 O
on 934 936 O
Monday 937 943 O
. 944 945 O

-DOCSTART- - - O

LONDON 21 27 I-LOC
, 28 29 O
Dec 30 33 O
7 34 35 O
( 36 37 O
Reuters 38 45 I-ORG
) 46 47 O
- 48 49 O
The 50 53 O
United 54 60 I-LOC
Kingdom 61 68 I-LOC
will 69 73 O
press 74 79 O
ahead 80 85 O
on 86 88 O
Monday 89 95 O
with 96 100 O
the 101 104 O
Internal 105 113 I-MISC
Market 114 120 I-MISC
Bill 121 125 I-MISC
that 126 130 O
breaches 131 139 O
the 140 143 O
Brexit 144 150 I-MISC
divorce 151 158 O
treaty 159 165 O
, 166 167 O
a 168 169 O
junior 170 176 O
foreign 177 184 O
office 185 191 O
minister 192 200 O
said 201 205 O
on 206 208 O
Monday 209 215 O
. 216 217 O

“ 219 220 O
The 221 224 O
Internal 225 233 I-MISC
Market 234 240 I-MISC
Bill 241 245 I-MISC
contains 246 254 O
really 255 261 O
important 262 271 O
clauses 272 279 O
that 280 284 O
protect 285 292 O
the 293 296 O
integrity 297 306 O
of 307 309 O
the 310 313 O
United 314 320 I-LOC
kingdom 321 328 I-LOC
, 329 330 O
” 331 332 O
junior 333 339 O
foreign 340 347 O
office 348 354 O
minister 355 363 O
James 364 369 I-PER
Cleverly 370 378 I-PER
told 379 383 O
Sky 384 387 I-ORG
. 388 389 O
“ 390 391 O

Ultimately 393 403 O
this 404 408 O
is 409 411 O
an 412 414 O
insurance 415 424 O
policy 425 431 O
, 432 433 O
it 434 436 O
’s 437 439 O
really 440 446 O
important 447 456 O
. 457 458 O
” 459 460 O

“ 462 463 O
It 464 466 O
’s 467 469 O
about 470 475 O
protecting 476 486 O
the 487 490 O
integrity 491 500 O
of 501 503 O
the 504 507 O
United 508 514 I-LOC
Kingdom 515 522 I-LOC
as 523 525 O
a 526 527 O
single 528 534 O
entity 535 541 O
, 542 543 O
” 544 545 O
he 546 548 O
said 549 553 O
. 554 555 O
“ 556 557 O

It 559 561 O
contains 562 570 O
clauses 571 578 O
that 579 583 O
we 584 586 O
may 587 590 O
need 591 595 O
to 596 598 O
rely 599 603 O
on 604 606 O
and 607 610 O
if 611 613 O
we 614 616 O
do 617 619 O
need 620 624 O
to 625 627 O
rely 628 632 O
on 633 635 O
them 636 640 O
, 641 642 O
better 643 649 O
that 650 654 O
they 655 659 O
’re 660 663 O
there 664 669 O
. 670 671 O
” 672 673 O

( 675 676 O
Reporting 677 686 O
by 687 689 O
Guy 690 693 I-PER
Faulconbridge 694 707 I-PER
and 708 711 O
Paul 712 716 I-PER
Sandle 717 723 I-PER
; 724 725 O
editing 726 733 O
by 734 736 O
Sarah 737 742 I-PER
Young 743 748 I-PER
) 749 750 O

-DOCSTART- - - O

( 21 22 O
For 23 26 O
a 27 28 O
Reuters 29 36 I-ORG
live 37 41 O
blog 42 46 O
on 47 49 O
U.S. 50 54 I-LOC
, 55 56 O
UK 57 59 I-LOC
and 60 63 O
European 64 72 I-MISC
stock 73 78 O
markets 79 86 O
, 87 88 O
click 89 94 O
LIVE/ 95 100 O
or 101 103 O
type 104 108 O
LIVE/ 109 114 O
in 115 117 O
a 118 119 O
news 120 124 O
window 125 131 O
) 132 133 O

* 135 136 O
Brexit 137 143 I-MISC
negotiations 144 156 O
enter 157 162 O
final 163 168 O
phase 169 174 O

* 176 177 O
Countrywide 178 189 I-MISC
surges 190 196 O
as 197 199 O
Connells 200 208 I-ORG
sweetens 209 217 O
buyout 218 224 O
bid 225 228 O

* 230 231 O
FTSE 232 236 I-MISC
100 237 240 I-MISC
up 241 243 O
0.3 244 247 O
% 248 249 O
, 250 251 O
FTSE 252 256 I-MISC
250 257 260 I-MISC
down 261 265 O
0.6 266 269 O
% 270 271 O
( 272 273 O
Adds 274 278 O
graphic 279 286 O
) 287 288 O

Dec 290 293 O
7 294 295 O
( 296 297 O
Reuters 298 305 I-ORG
) 306 307 O
- 308 309 O
London-listed 310 323 I-MISC
mid-caps 324 332 O
fell 333 337 O
on 338 340 O
Monday 341 347 O
on 348 350 O
fears 351 356 O
that 357 361 O
Britain 362 369 I-LOC
’s 370 372 O
transition 373 383 O
period 384 390 O
out 391 394 O
of 395 397 O
the 398 401 O
European 402 410 I-ORG
Union 411 416 I-ORG
would 417 422 O
expire 423 429 O
without 430 437 O
a 438 439 O
free 440 444 O
trade 445 450 O
deal 451 455 O
in 456 458 O
place 459 464 O
, 465 466 O
while 467 472 O
Countrywide 473 484 I-MISC
surged 485 491 O
to 492 494 O
a 495 496 O
near 497 501 O
ten-month 502 511 O
high 512 516 O
following 517 526 O
a 527 528 O
sweetened 529 538 O
buyout 539 545 O
offer 546 551 O
. 552 553 O

The 555 558 O
mid-cap 559 566 O
FTSE 567 571 I-MISC
250 572 575 I-MISC
, 576 577 O
considered 578 588 O
a 589 590 O
barometer 591 600 O
of 601 603 O
Brexit 604 610 I-MISC
sentiment 611 620 O
, 621 622 O
lost 623 627 O
0.6 628 631 O
% 632 633 O
as 634 636 O
Britain 637 644 I-LOC
and 645 648 O
the 649 652 O
EU 653 655 I-ORG
made 656 660 O
a 661 662 O
last-ditch 663 673 O
attempt 674 681 O
to 682 684 O
bridge 685 691 O
significant 692 703 O
differences 704 715 O
and 716 719 O
reach 720 725 O
a 726 727 O
deal 728 732 O
to 733 735 O
avoid 736 741 O
a 742 743 O
disorderly 744 754 O
exit 755 759 O
in 760 762 O
just 763 767 O
24 768 770 O
days 771 775 O
. 776 777 O

The 779 782 O
export-heavy 783 795 O
FTSE 796 800 I-MISC
100 801 804 I-MISC
was 805 808 O
up 809 811 O
0.3 812 815 O
% 816 817 O
as 818 820 O
no-deal 821 828 O
Brexit 829 835 I-MISC
worries 836 843 O
pressured 844 853 O
the 854 857 O
pound 858 863 O
. 864 865 O

Autos 867 872 O
, 873 874 O
economically-sensitive 875 897 O
banks 898 903 O
and 904 907 O
real 908 912 O
estate 913 919 O
firms 920 925 O
were 926 930 O
among 931 936 O
the 937 940 O
biggest 941 948 O
decliners 949 958 O
in 959 961 O
morning 962 969 O
trading 970 977 O
. 978 979 O

“ 981 982 O
The 983 986 O
market 987 993 O
is 994 996 O
getting 997 1004 O
a 1005 1006 O
little 1007 1013 O
bit 1014 1017 O
anxious 1018 1025 O
right 1026 1031 O
now 1032 1035 O
, 1036 1037 O
” 1038 1039 O
said 1040 1044 O
Stefan 1045 1051 I-PER
Koopman 1052 1059 I-PER
, 1060 1061 O
senior 1062 1068 O
market 1069 1075 O
economist 1076 1085 O
at 1086 1088 O
Rabobank 1089 1097 I-ORG
. 1098 1099 O

“ 1101 1102 O
There 1103 1108 O
has 1109 1112 O
been 1113 1117 O
progress 1118 1126 O
on 1127 1129 O
a 1130 1131 O
technical 1132 1141 O
level 1142 1147 O
behind 1148 1154 O
the 1155 1158 O
scenes 1159 1165 O
, 1166 1167 O
but 1168 1171 O
there 1172 1177 O
is 1178 1180 O
no 1181 1183 O
political 1184 1193 O
agreement 1194 1203 O
yet 1204 1207 O
. 1208 1209 O
” 1210 1211 O

British 1213 1220 I-MISC
and 1221 1224 O
EU 1225 1227 I-ORG
negotiators 1228 1239 O
have 1240 1244 O
been 1245 1249 O
haggling 1250 1258 O
for 1259 1262 O
weeks 1263 1268 O
over 1269 1273 O
fishing 1274 1281 O
rights 1282 1288 O
, 1289 1290 O
ensuring 1291 1299 O
fair 1300 1304 O
competition 1305 1316 O
for 1317 1320 O
companies 1321 1330 O
and 1331 1334 O
ways 1335 1339 O
to 1340 1342 O
solve 1343 1348 O
future 1349 1355 O
disputes 1356 1364 O
. 1365 1366 O

Investment 1368 1378 O
bank 1379 1383 O
JPMorgan 1384 1392 I-ORG
said 1393 1397 O
odds 1398 1402 O
of 1403 1405 O
a 1406 1407 O
no-trade 1408 1416 O
deal 1417 1421 O
exit 1422 1426 O
had 1427 1430 O
risen 1431 1436 O
to 1437 1439 O
more 1440 1444 O
than 1445 1449 O
30 1450 1452 O
% 1453 1454 O
from 1455 1459 O
20 1460 1462 O
% 1463 1464 O
. 1465 1466 O

Still 1468 1473 O
, 1474 1475 O
the 1476 1479 O
FTSE 1480 1484 I-MISC
100 1485 1488 I-MISC
is 1489 1491 O
on 1492 1494 O
track 1495 1500 O
to 1501 1503 O
record 1504 1510 O
its 1511 1514 O
biggest 1515 1522 O
quarterly 1523 1532 O
gain 1533 1537 O
since 1538 1543 O
2010 1544 1548 O
after 1549 1554 O
being 1555 1560 O
boosted 1561 1568 O
by 1569 1571 O
hopes 1572 1577 O
that 1578 1582 O
effective 1583 1592 O
COVID-19 1593 1601 I-MISC
vaccines 1602 1610 O
would 1611 1616 O
soon 1617 1621 O
be 1622 1624 O
available 1625 1634 O
and 1635 1638 O
speed 1639 1644 O
up 1645 1647 O
an 1648 1650 O
economic 1651 1659 O
recovery 1660 1668 O
next 1669 1673 O
year 1674 1678 O
. 1679 1680 O

Data 1682 1686 O
on 1687 1689 O
Monday 1690 1696 O
showed 1697 1703 O
UK 1704 1706 I-LOC
house 1707 1712 O
prices 1713 1719 O
last 1720 1724 O
month 1725 1730 O
posted 1731 1737 O
their 1738 1743 O
biggest 1744 1751 O
annual 1752 1758 O
increase 1759 1767 O
since 1768 1773 O
June 1774 1778 O
2016 1779 1783 O
, 1784 1785 O
as 1786 1788 O
people 1789 1795 O
sought 1796 1802 O
to 1803 1805 O
move 1806 1810 O
into 1811 1815 O
bigger 1816 1822 O
houses 1823 1829 O
following 1830 1839 O
COVID-19-driven 1840 1855 I-MISC
lockdowns 1856 1865 O
. 1866 1867 O

In 1869 1871 O
company 1872 1879 O
news 1880 1884 O
, 1885 1886 O
Countrywide 1887 1898 I-MISC
Plc 1899 1902 I-MISC
surged 1903 1909 O
21.3 1910 1914 O
% 1915 1916 O
after 1917 1922 O
real 1923 1927 O
estate 1928 1934 O
management 1935 1945 O
firm 1946 1950 O
Connells 1951 1959 I-ORG
Ltd 1960 1963 I-ORG
said 1964 1968 O
it 1969 1971 O
had 1972 1975 O
raised 1976 1982 O
its 1983 1986 O
buyout 1987 1993 O
offer 1994 1999 O
for 2000 2003 O
the 2004 2007 O
British 2008 2015 I-MISC
firm 2016 2020 O
to 2021 2023 O
164.5 2024 2029 O
million 2030 2037 O
pounds 2038 2044 O
( 2045 2046 O
$ 2047 2048 O
219.99 2049 2055 O
million 2056 2063 O
) 2064 2065 O
. 2066 2067 O

Fashion 2069 2076 O
retailer 2077 2085 O
Ted 2086 2089 I-MISC
Baker 2090 2095 I-MISC
tumbled 2096 2103 O
5.7 2104 2107 O
% 2108 2109 O
as 2110 2112 O
its 2113 2116 O
half-year 2117 2126 O
losses 2127 2133 O
ballooned 2134 2143 O
due 2144 2147 O
to 2148 2150 O
coronavirus-led 2151 2166 O
lockdowns 2167 2176 O
denting 2177 2184 O
retail 2185 2191 O
sales 2192 2197 O
. 2198 2199 O

-DOCSTART- - - O

FILE 21 25 O
PHOTO 26 31 O
: 32 33 O
French 34 40 I-MISC
driver 41 47 O
Sebastien 48 57 I-PER
Ogier 58 63 I-PER
during 64 70 O
the 71 74 O
Neste 75 80 I-MISC
Rally 81 86 I-MISC
in 87 89 O
Jyväskylä 90 99 I-LOC
, 100 101 O
Finland 102 109 I-LOC
August 110 116 O
1 117 118 O
, 119 120 O
2019 121 125 O
. 126 127 O

Lehtikuva 129 138 I-ORG
/ 139 140 O
Roni 141 145 I-PER
Rekomaa 146 153 I-PER
/ 154 155 O
via 156 159 O
REUTERS 160 167 I-ORG

MILAN 169 174 I-LOC
( 175 176 O
Reuters 177 184 I-ORG
) 185 186 O
- 187 188 O
Sebastien 189 198 I-PER
Ogier 199 204 I-PER
clinched 205 213 O
the 214 217 O
world 218 223 O
rally 224 229 O
championship 230 242 O
for 243 246 O
the 247 250 O
seventh 251 258 O
time 259 263 O
in 264 266 O
eight 267 272 O
years 273 278 O
after 279 284 O
the 285 288 O
Frenchman 289 298 I-MISC
won 299 302 O
the 303 306 O
season-ending 307 320 O
Rally 321 326 I-MISC
Monza 327 332 I-MISC
on 333 335 O
Sunday 336 342 O
. 343 344 O

Toyota 346 352 I-ORG
team 353 357 O
mate 358 362 O
Elfyn 363 368 I-PER
Evans 369 374 I-PER
, 375 376 O
who 377 380 O
had 381 384 O
a 385 386 O
14-point 387 395 O
lead 396 400 O
before 401 407 O
the 408 411 O
final 412 417 O
round 418 423 O
in 424 426 O
northern 427 435 O
Italy 436 441 I-LOC
, 442 443 O
crashed 444 451 O
out 452 455 O
on 456 458 O
Saturday 459 467 O
but 468 471 O
returned 472 480 O
for 481 484 O
the 485 488 O
final 489 494 O
three 495 500 O
stages 501 507 O
at 508 510 O
the 511 514 O
Monza 515 520 I-LOC
circuit 521 528 I-LOC
on 529 531 O
Sunday 532 538 O
. 539 540 O

Ogier 542 547 I-PER
won 548 551 O
the 552 555 O
rally 556 561 O
by 562 564 O
13.9 565 569 O
seconds 570 577 O
, 578 579 O
with 580 584 O
Hyundai 585 592 I-ORG
’s 593 595 O
outgoing 596 604 O
champion 605 613 O
Ott 614 617 I-PER
Tanak 618 623 I-PER
runner-up 624 633 O
to 634 636 O
finish 637 643 O
third 644 649 O
overall 650 657 O
in 658 660 O
the 661 664 O
championship 665 677 O
. 678 679 O

Ogier 681 686 I-PER
, 687 688 O
who 689 692 O
has 693 696 O
now 697 700 O
won 701 704 O
titles 705 711 O
with 712 716 O
three 717 722 O
different 723 732 O
manufacturers 733 746 O
after 747 752 O
four 753 757 O
with 758 762 O
Volkswagen 763 773 I-ORG
and 774 777 O
two 778 781 O
for 782 785 O
Ford 786 790 I-ORG
, 791 792 O
finished 793 801 O
eight 802 807 O
points 808 814 O
clear 815 820 O
of 821 823 O
Welshman 824 832 I-MISC
Evans 833 838 I-PER
. 839 840 O

Evans 842 847 I-PER
finished 848 856 O
outside 857 864 O
the 865 868 O
top 869 872 O
10 873 875 O
but 876 879 O
banked 880 886 O
three 887 892 O
points 893 899 O
from 900 904 O
the 905 908 O
final 909 914 O
Power 915 920 I-MISC
Stage 921 926 I-MISC
. 927 928 O

“ 930 931 O
It 932 934 O
was 935 938 O
a 939 940 O
difficult 941 950 O
weekend 951 958 O
and 959 962 O
this 963 967 O
last 968 972 O
stage 973 978 O
was 979 982 O
not 983 986 O
enjoyable 987 996 O
, 997 998 O
” 999 1000 O
said 1001 1005 O
Ogier 1006 1011 I-PER
, 1012 1013 O
whose 1014 1019 O
car 1020 1023 O
’s 1024 1026 O
wipers 1027 1033 O
were 1034 1038 O
faulty 1039 1045 O
on 1046 1048 O
the 1049 1052 O
final 1053 1058 O
stage 1059 1064 O
. 1065 1066 O

“ 1068 1069 O
We 1070 1072 O
feel 1073 1077 O
sorry 1078 1083 O
for 1084 1087 O
Elfyn 1088 1093 I-PER
. 1094 1095 O

We 1097 1099 O
had 1100 1103 O
great 1104 1109 O
fun 1110 1113 O
fighting 1114 1122 O
each 1123 1127 O
other 1128 1133 O
this 1134 1138 O
season 1139 1145 O
, 1146 1147 O
and 1148 1151 O
I 1152 1153 O
am 1154 1156 O
sure 1157 1161 O
next 1162 1166 O
year 1167 1171 O
will 1172 1176 O
be 1177 1179 O
the 1180 1183 O
same 1184 1188 O
. 1189 1190 O
” 1191 1192 O

Tanak 1194 1199 I-PER
finished 1200 1208 O
1.4 1209 1212 O
seconds 1213 1220 O
ahead 1221 1226 O
of 1227 1229 O
Spanish 1230 1237 I-MISC
team 1238 1242 O
mate 1243 1247 O
Dani 1248 1252 I-PER
Sordo 1253 1258 I-PER
, 1259 1260 O
to 1261 1263 O
clinch 1264 1270 O
the 1271 1274 O
manufacturers 1275 1288 O
’ 1289 1290 O
title 1291 1296 O
for 1297 1300 O
Hyundai 1301 1308 I-ORG
for 1309 1312 O
the 1313 1316 O
second 1317 1323 O
season 1324 1330 O
in 1331 1333 O
a 1334 1335 O
row 1336 1339 O
. 1340 1341 O

-DOCSTART- - - O

( 21 22 O
Reuters 23 30 I-ORG
) 31 32 O
- 33 34 O
An 35 37 O
‘ 38 39 O
overwhelmed 40 51 O
’ 52 53 O
Mick 54 58 I-PER
Schumacher 59 69 I-PER
graduated 70 79 O
to 80 82 O
Formula 83 90 I-MISC
One 91 94 I-MISC
as 95 97 O
the 98 101 O
2020 102 106 O
Formula 107 114 I-MISC
Two 115 118 I-MISC
champion 119 127 O
on 128 130 O
Sunday 131 137 O
despite 138 145 O
failing 146 153 O
to 154 156 O
score 157 162 O
in 163 165 O
his 166 169 O
last 170 174 O
race 175 179 O
before 180 186 O
joining 187 194 O
the 195 198 O
U.S.-owned 199 209 I-MISC
Haas 210 214 I-ORG
F1 215 217 I-MISC
team 218 222 O
. 223 224 O

FILE 226 230 O
PHOTO 231 236 O
: 237 238 O
Racing 239 245 O
driver 246 252 O
Mick 253 257 I-PER
Schumacher 258 268 I-PER
attends 269 276 O
an 277 279 O
event 280 285 O
to 286 288 O
celebrate 289 298 O
90 299 301 O
years 302 307 O
of 308 310 O
Italian 311 318 I-MISC
premium 319 326 O
sports 327 333 O
car 334 337 O
maker 338 343 O
Ferrari 344 351 I-ORG
racing 352 358 O
team 359 363 O
at 364 366 O
Milan 367 372 I-LOC
's 373 375 O
Duomo 376 381 I-LOC
square 382 388 I-LOC
, 389 390 O
in 391 393 O
Milan 394 399 I-LOC
, 400 401 O
Italy 402 407 I-LOC
September 408 417 O
4 418 419 O
, 420 421 O
2019 422 426 O
. 427 428 O

REUTERS 430 437 I-ORG
/ 438 439 O
Flavio 440 446 I-PER
lo 447 449 I-PER
Scalzo 450 456 I-PER
/ 457 458 O
File 459 463 O
Photo 464 469 O

The 471 474 O
21-year-old 475 486 O
son 487 490 O
of 491 493 O
seven-time 494 504 O
world 505 510 O
champion 511 519 O
and 520 523 O
Ferrari 524 531 I-ORG
great 532 537 O
Michael 538 545 I-PER
was 546 549 O
18th 550 554 O
in 555 557 O
a 558 559 O
sprint 560 566 O
race 567 571 O
won 572 575 O
by 576 578 O
Indian 579 585 I-MISC
driver 586 592 O
Jehan 593 598 I-PER
Daruvala 599 607 I-PER
while 608 613 O
his 614 617 O
sole 618 622 O
title 623 628 O
rival 629 634 O
, 635 636 O
Callum 637 643 I-PER
Ilott 644 649 I-PER
, 650 651 O
finished 652 660 O
10th 661 665 O
with 666 670 O
only 671 675 O
the 676 679 O
top 680 683 O
eight 684 689 O
scoring 690 697 O
. 698 699 O

Schumacher 701 711 I-PER
signed 712 718 O
off 719 722 O
with 723 727 O
215 728 731 O
points 732 738 O
, 739 740 O
14 741 743 O
clear 744 749 O
of 750 752 O
Briton 753 759 I-PER
Ilott 760 765 I-PER
, 766 767 O
with 768 772 O
Japan 773 778 I-LOC
’s 779 781 O
Yuki 782 786 I-PER
Tsunoda 787 794 I-PER
, 795 796 O
now 797 800 O
expected 801 809 O
to 810 812 O
move 813 817 O
up 818 820 O
to 821 823 O
Formula 824 831 I-MISC
One 832 835 I-MISC
with 836 840 O
Red 841 844 I-ORG
Bull 845 849 I-ORG
’s 850 852 O
Honda-powered 853 866 I-MISC
AlphaTauri 867 877 I-ORG
team 878 882 O
, 883 884 O
a 885 886 O
further 887 894 O
point 895 900 O
behind 901 907 O
. 908 909 O

Tyre 911 915 O
damage 916 922 O
forced 923 929 O
the 930 933 O
German 934 940 I-MISC
to 941 943 O
pit 944 947 O
after 948 953 O
15 954 956 O
laps 957 961 O
, 962 963 O
sending 964 971 O
him 972 975 O
to 976 978 O
the 979 982 O
back 983 987 O
of 988 990 O
the 991 994 O
field 995 1000 O
. 1001 1002 O

“ 1004 1005 O
It 1006 1008 O
would 1009 1014 O
feel 1015 1019 O
or 1020 1022 O
sound 1023 1028 O
a 1029 1030 O
lot 1031 1034 O
better 1035 1041 O
if 1042 1044 O
I 1045 1046 O
had 1047 1050 O
a 1051 1052 O
good 1053 1057 O
race 1058 1062 O
today 1063 1068 O
, 1069 1070 O
” 1071 1072 O
Schumacher 1073 1083 I-PER
said 1084 1088 O
of 1089 1091 O
the 1092 1095 O
title 1096 1101 O
, 1102 1103 O
achieved 1104 1112 O
with 1113 1117 O
two 1118 1121 O
wins 1122 1126 O
and 1127 1130 O
no 1131 1133 O
poles 1134 1139 O
but 1140 1143 O
plenty 1144 1150 O
of 1151 1153 O
consistency 1154 1165 O
. 1166 1167 O
“ 1168 1169 O

Nevertheless 1171 1183 O
, 1184 1185 O
we 1186 1188 O
did 1189 1192 O
enough 1193 1199 O
. 1200 1201 O

“ 1203 1204 O
To 1205 1207 O
be 1208 1210 O
honest 1211 1217 O
, 1218 1219 O
I 1220 1221 O
’m 1222 1224 O
a 1225 1226 O
bit 1227 1230 O
overwhelmed 1231 1242 O
, 1243 1244 O
” 1245 1246 O
he 1247 1249 O
added 1250 1255 O
. 1256 1257 O
“ 1258 1259 O

I 1261 1262 O
do 1263 1265 O
n’t 1266 1269 O
really 1270 1276 O
understand 1277 1287 O
or 1288 1290 O
feel 1291 1295 O
like 1296 1300 O
a 1301 1302 O
champion 1303 1311 O
yet 1312 1315 O
. 1316 1317 O

It 1319 1321 O
’s 1322 1324 O
going 1325 1330 O
to 1331 1333 O
take 1334 1338 O
a 1339 1340 O
few 1341 1344 O
days 1345 1349 O
maybe 1350 1355 O
. 1356 1357 O

“ 1359 1360 O
We 1361 1363 O
pitted 1364 1370 O
, 1371 1372 O
we 1373 1375 O
did 1376 1379 O
n’t 1380 1383 O
manage 1384 1390 O
to 1391 1393 O
get 1394 1397 O
back 1398 1402 O
to 1403 1405 O
the 1406 1409 O
front 1410 1415 O
but 1416 1419 O
nevertheless 1420 1432 O
we 1433 1435 O
are 1436 1439 O
champions 1440 1449 O
now 1450 1453 O
today 1454 1459 O
, 1460 1461 O
and 1462 1465 O
that 1466 1470 O
’s 1471 1473 O
what 1474 1478 O
people 1479 1485 O
will 1486 1490 O
remember 1491 1499 O
. 1500 1501 O

They 1503 1507 O
will 1508 1512 O
forget 1513 1519 O
this 1520 1524 O
race 1525 1529 O
today 1530 1535 O
and 1536 1539 O
only 1540 1544 O
see 1545 1548 O
the 1549 1552 O
good 1553 1557 O
times 1558 1563 O
of 1564 1566 O
this 1567 1571 O
year 1572 1576 O
, 1577 1578 O
and 1579 1582 O
I 1583 1584 O
will 1585 1589 O
too 1590 1593 O
. 1594 1595 O
” 1596 1597 O

Michael 1599 1606 I-PER
Schumacher 1607 1617 I-PER
retired 1618 1625 O
in 1626 1628 O
2012 1629 1633 O
after 1634 1639 O
a 1640 1641 O
three-season 1642 1654 O
comeback 1655 1663 O
with 1664 1668 O
Mercedes 1669 1677 I-ORG
and 1678 1681 O
has 1682 1685 O
not 1686 1689 O
been 1690 1694 O
seen 1695 1699 O
in 1700 1702 O
public 1703 1709 O
since 1710 1715 O
suffering 1716 1725 O
severe 1726 1732 O
head 1733 1737 O
injuries 1738 1746 O
in 1747 1749 O
a 1750 1751 O
skiing 1752 1758 O
accident 1759 1767 O
in 1768 1770 O
the 1771 1774 O
French 1775 1781 I-LOC
Alps 1782 1786 I-LOC
in 1787 1789 O
2013 1790 1794 O
. 1795 1796 O

Mick 1798 1802 I-PER
was 1803 1806 O
European 1807 1815 I-MISC
F3 1816 1818 I-MISC
champion 1819 1827 O
in 1828 1830 O
2018 1831 1835 O
and 1836 1839 O
joins 1840 1845 O
Charles 1846 1853 I-PER
Leclerc 1854 1861 I-PER
and 1862 1865 O
George 1866 1872 I-PER
Russell 1873 1880 I-PER
, 1881 1882 O
now 1883 1886 O
with 1887 1891 O
Ferrari 1892 1899 I-ORG
and 1900 1903 O
Williams 1904 1912 I-ORG
respectively 1913 1925 O
, 1926 1927 O
as 1928 1930 O
recent 1931 1937 O
F2 1938 1940 I-MISC
champions 1941 1950 O
who 1951 1954 O
have 1955 1959 O
stepped 1960 1967 O
up 1968 1970 O
to 1971 1973 O
F1 1974 1976 I-MISC
. 1977 1978 O

The 1980 1983 O
series 1984 1990 O
was 1991 1994 O
previously 1995 2005 O
known 2006 2011 O
as 2012 2014 O
GP2 2015 2018 I-MISC
. 2019 2020 O

A 2022 2023 O
Ferrari 2024 2031 I-ORG
Academy 2032 2039 I-ORG
driver 2040 2046 O
, 2047 2048 O
Schumacher 2049 2059 I-PER
was 2060 2063 O
announced 2064 2073 O
by 2074 2076 O
Ferrari-powered 2077 2092 I-MISC
Haas 2093 2097 I-ORG
last 2098 2102 O
Wednesday 2103 2112 O
as 2113 2115 O
one 2116 2119 O
of 2120 2122 O
their 2123 2128 O
2021 2129 2133 O
race 2134 2138 O
drivers 2139 2146 O
along 2147 2152 O
with 2153 2157 O
Russian 2158 2165 I-MISC
Nikita 2166 2172 I-PER
Mazepin 2173 2180 I-PER
. 2181 2182 O

He 2184 2186 O
will 2187 2191 O
bring 2192 2197 O
a 2198 2199 O
sizeable 2200 2208 O
support 2209 2216 O
with 2217 2221 O
him 2222 2225 O
to 2226 2228 O
Formula 2229 2236 I-MISC
One 2237 2240 I-MISC
as 2241 2243 O
son 2244 2247 O
of 2248 2250 O
one 2251 2254 O
of 2255 2257 O
the 2258 2261 O
greatest 2262 2270 O
drivers 2271 2278 O
of 2279 2281 O
all 2282 2285 O
time 2286 2290 O
. 2291 2292 O

The 2294 2297 O
German 2298 2304 I-MISC
already 2305 2312 O
has 2313 2316 O
1.3 2317 2320 O
million 2321 2328 O
followers 2329 2338 O
on 2339 2341 O
Instagram 2342 2351 I-MISC
, 2352 2353 O
and 2354 2357 O
more 2358 2362 O
than 2363 2367 O
180,000 2368 2375 O
on 2376 2378 O
Twitter 2379 2386 I-MISC
and 2387 2390 O
can 2391 2394 O
count 2395 2400 O
on 2401 2403 O
strong 2404 2410 O
commercial 2411 2421 O
backing 2422 2429 O
. 2430 2431 O

According 2433 2442 O
to 2443 2445 O
Nielsen 2446 2453 I-ORG
Sports 2454 2460 I-ORG
, 2461 2462 O
a 2463 2464 O
majority 2465 2473 O
of 2474 2476 O
Schumacher 2477 2487 I-PER
’s 2488 2490 O
fanbase 2491 2498 O
is 2499 2501 O
Italian 2502 2509 I-MISC
with 2510 2514 O
Germany 2515 2522 I-LOC
accounting 2523 2533 O
for 2534 2537 O
only 2538 2542 O
10 2543 2545 O
% 2546 2547 O
of 2548 2550 O
that 2551 2555 O
following 2556 2565 O
. 2566 2567 O

“ 2569 2570 O
Bringing 2571 2579 O
in 2580 2582 O
Mick 2583 2587 I-PER
Schumacher 2588 2598 I-PER
will 2599 2603 O
increase 2604 2612 O
Haas 2613 2617 I-ORG
’ 2618 2619 O
global 2620 2626 O
commercial 2627 2637 O
viability 2638 2647 O
, 2648 2649 O
” 2650 2651 O
said 2652 2656 O
Nielsen 2657 2664 I-ORG
Sports 2665 2671 I-ORG
’ 2672 2673 O
senior 2674 2680 O
vice-president 2681 2695 O
of 2696 2698 O
global 2699 2705 O
motorsports 2706 2717 O
Nigel 2718 2723 I-PER
Geach 2724 2729 I-PER
. 2730 2731 O

“ 2733 2734 O
We 2735 2737 O
expect 2738 2744 O
sponsorship 2745 2756 O
appetite 2757 2765 O
to 2766 2768 O
be 2769 2771 O
substantial 2772 2783 O
. 2784 2785 O

There 2787 2792 O
is 2793 2795 O
a 2796 2797 O
real 2798 2802 O
incentive 2803 2812 O
for 2813 2816 O
his 2817 2820 O
father 2821 2827 O
’s 2828 2830 O
old 2831 2834 O
sponsors 2835 2843 O
to 2844 2846 O
be 2847 2849 O
involved 2850 2858 O
, 2859 2860 O
as 2861 2863 O
well 2864 2868 O
as 2869 2871 O
interest 2872 2880 O
from 2881 2885 O
new 2886 2889 O
parties 2890 2897 O
. 2898 2899 O
” 2900 2901 O

-DOCSTART- - - O

( 21 22 O
Reuters 23 30 I-ORG
) 31 32 O
- 33 34 O
Michigan 35 43 I-LOC
Secretary 44 53 O
of 54 56 O
State 57 62 O
Jocelyn 63 70 I-PER
Benson 71 77 I-PER
said 78 82 O
dozens 83 89 O
of 90 92 O
armed 93 98 O
protesters 99 109 O
gathered 110 118 O
in 119 121 O
a 122 123 O
threatening 124 135 O
manner 136 142 O
outside 143 150 O
her 151 154 O
home 155 159 O
on 160 162 O
Saturday 163 171 O
evening 172 179 O
chanting 180 188 O
“ 189 190 O
bogus 191 196 O
” 197 198 O
claims 199 205 O
about 206 211 O
electoral 212 221 O
fraud 222 227 O
. 228 229 O

Slideshow 231 240 O
( 241 242 O
2 243 244 O
images 245 251 O
) 252 253 O

Michigan 255 263 I-LOC
officials 264 273 O
last 274 278 O
month 279 284 O
certified 285 294 O
the 295 298 O
state 299 304 O
’s 305 307 O
election 308 316 O
results 317 324 O
showing 325 332 O
President-elect 333 348 O
Joe 349 352 I-PER
Biden 353 358 I-PER
had 359 362 O
won 363 366 O
Michigan 367 375 I-LOC
, 376 377 O
one 378 381 O
of 382 384 O
a 385 386 O
handful 387 394 O
of 395 397 O
key 398 401 O
battleground 402 414 O
states 415 421 O
, 422 423 O
in 424 426 O
the 427 430 O
course 431 437 O
of 438 440 O
his 441 444 O
Nov. 445 449 O
3 450 451 O
election 452 460 O
victory 461 468 O
. 469 470 O

President 472 481 O
Donald 482 488 I-PER
Trump 489 494 I-PER
has 495 498 O
repeatedly 499 509 O
claimed 510 517 O
, 518 519 O
contrary 520 528 O
to 529 531 O
evidence 532 540 O
, 541 542 O
that 543 547 O
the 548 551 O
outcome 552 559 O
was 560 563 O
marred 564 570 O
by 571 573 O
widespread 574 584 O
fraud 585 590 O
in 591 593 O
multiple 594 602 O
states 603 609 O
. 610 611 O

State 613 618 O
and 619 622 O
federal 623 630 O
officials 631 640 O
have 641 645 O
repeatedly 646 656 O
stated 657 663 O
that 664 668 O
there 669 674 O
is 675 677 O
no 678 680 O
evidence 681 689 O
of 690 692 O
fraud 693 698 O
on 699 701 O
any 702 705 O
significant 706 717 O
scale 718 723 O
, 724 725 O
and 726 729 O
Biden 730 735 I-PER
is 736 738 O
to 739 741 O
sworn 742 747 O
into 748 752 O
office 753 759 O
on 760 762 O
Jan. 763 767 O
20 768 770 O
. 771 772 O

The 774 777 O
protesters 778 788 O
who 789 792 O
rallied 793 800 O
outside 801 808 O
Benson 809 815 I-PER
's 816 818 O
home 819 823 O
held 824 828 O
up 829 831 O
placards 832 840 O
saying 841 847 O
" 848 849 O
Stop 850 854 I-MISC
the 855 858 I-MISC
Steal 859 864 I-MISC
" 865 866 O
and 867 870 O
chanted 871 878 O
the 879 882 O
same 883 887 O
message 888 895 O
, 896 897 O
according 898 907 O
here 908 912 O
to 913 915 O
various 916 923 O
clips 924 929 O
uploaded 930 938 O
on 939 941 O
social 942 948 O
media 949 954 O
. 955 956 O

In 958 960 O
a 961 962 O
Twitter 963 970 I-MISC
statement 971 980 O
on 981 983 O
Sunday 984 990 O
, 991 992 O
Benson 993 999 I-PER
said 1000 1004 O
the 1005 1008 O
protesters 1009 1019 O
were 1020 1024 O
trying 1025 1031 O
to 1032 1034 O
spread 1035 1041 O
false 1042 1047 O
information 1048 1059 O
about 1060 1065 O
the 1066 1069 O
security 1070 1078 O
and 1079 1082 O
accuracy 1083 1091 O
of 1092 1094 O
the 1095 1098 O
U.S. 1099 1103 I-LOC
election 1104 1112 O
system 1113 1119 O
. 1120 1121 O
“ 1122 1123 O

The 1125 1128 O
demands 1129 1136 O
made 1137 1141 O
outside 1142 1149 O
my 1150 1152 O
home 1153 1157 O
were 1158 1162 O
unambiguous 1163 1174 O
, 1175 1176 O
loud 1177 1181 O
and 1182 1185 O
threatening 1186 1197 O
. 1198 1199 O
” 1200 1201 O

Michigan 1203 1211 I-LOC
Attorney 1212 1220 O
General 1221 1228 O
Dana 1229 1233 I-PER
Nessel 1234 1240 I-PER
, 1241 1242 O
in 1243 1245 O
a 1246 1247 O
separate 1248 1256 O
Twitter 1257 1264 I-MISC
post 1265 1269 O
, 1270 1271 O
accused 1272 1279 O
the 1280 1283 O
pro-Trump 1284 1293 I-MISC
demonstrators 1294 1307 O
of 1308 1310 O
“ 1311 1312 O
mob-like 1313 1321 O
behavior 1322 1330 O
( 1331 1332 O
that 1333 1337 O
) 1338 1339 O
is 1340 1342 O
an 1343 1345 O
affront 1346 1353 O
to 1354 1356 O
basic 1357 1362 O
morality 1363 1371 O
and 1372 1375 O
decency 1376 1383 O
” 1384 1385 O
. 1386 1387 O

“ 1389 1390 O
Anyone 1391 1397 O
can 1398 1401 O
air 1402 1405 O
legitimate 1406 1416 O
grievances 1417 1427 O
to 1428 1430 O
Secretary 1431 1440 O
Benson 1441 1447 I-PER
’s 1448 1450 O
office 1451 1457 O
through 1458 1465 O
civil 1466 1471 O
and 1472 1475 O
democratic 1476 1486 O
means 1487 1492 O
, 1493 1494 O
but 1495 1498 O
terrorizing 1499 1510 O
children 1511 1519 O
and 1520 1523 O
families 1524 1532 O
in 1533 1535 O
their 1536 1541 O
own 1542 1545 O
homes 1546 1551 O
is 1552 1554 O
not 1555 1558 O
activism 1559 1567 O
. 1568 1569 O
” 1570 1571 O

Benson 1573 1579 I-PER
added 1580 1585 O
: 1586 1587 O
“ 1588 1589 O
They 1590 1594 O
targeted 1595 1603 O
me 1604 1606 O
in 1607 1609 O
my 1610 1612 O
role 1613 1617 O
as 1618 1620 O
Michigan 1621 1629 I-LOC
’s 1630 1632 O
Chief 1633 1638 O
Election 1639 1647 O
Officer 1648 1655 O
. 1656 1657 O

But 1659 1662 O
the 1663 1666 O
threats 1667 1674 O
of 1675 1677 O
those 1678 1683 O
gathered 1684 1692 O
were 1693 1697 O
n’t 1698 1701 O
actually 1702 1710 O
aimed 1711 1716 O
at 1717 1719 O
me 1720 1722 O
- 1723 1724 O
or 1725 1727 O
any 1728 1731 O
other 1732 1737 O
elected 1738 1745 O
officials 1746 1755 O
in 1756 1758 O
this 1759 1763 O
state 1764 1769 O
. 1770 1771 O

They 1773 1777 O
were 1778 1782 O
aimed 1783 1788 O
at 1789 1791 O
the 1792 1795 O
voters 1796 1802 O
. 1803 1804 O
” 1805 1806 O

Michigan 1808 1816 I-LOC
Governor 1817 1825 O
Gretchen 1826 1834 I-PER
Whitmer 1835 1842 I-PER
, 1843 1844 O
who 1845 1848 O
has 1849 1852 O
clashed 1853 1860 O
publicly 1861 1869 O
with 1870 1874 O
Trump 1875 1880 I-PER
over 1881 1885 O
state 1886 1891 O
coronavirus 1892 1903 O
restrictions 1904 1916 O
, 1917 1918 O
was 1919 1922 O
the 1923 1926 O
target 1927 1933 O
of 1934 1936 O
a 1937 1938 O
kidnapping 1939 1949 O
plot 1950 1954 O
by 1955 1957 O
a 1958 1959 O
far-right 1960 1969 O
militia 1970 1977 O
group 1978 1983 O
during 1984 1990 O
the 1991 1994 O
election 1995 2003 O
campaign 2004 2012 O
, 2013 2014 O
prosecutors 2015 2026 O
said 2027 2031 O
in 2032 2034 O
October 2035 2042 O
. 2043 2044 O

Michigan 2046 2054 I-LOC
, 2055 2056 O
one 2057 2060 O
of 2061 2063 O
a 2064 2065 O
handful 2066 2073 O
of 2074 2076 O
key 2077 2080 O
swing 2081 2086 O
state 2087 2092 O
in 2093 2095 O
the 2096 2099 O
2020 2100 2104 O
presidential 2105 2117 O
race 2118 2122 O
, 2123 2124 O
was 2125 2128 O
a 2129 2130 O
target 2131 2137 O
of 2138 2140 O
agitation 2141 2150 O
by 2151 2153 O
Trump 2154 2159 I-PER
and 2160 2163 O
right-wing 2164 2174 O
supporters 2175 2185 O
against 2186 2193 O
stay-at-home 2194 2206 O
orders 2207 2213 O
Whitmer 2214 2221 I-PER
imposed 2222 2229 O
earlier 2230 2237 O
this 2238 2242 O
year 2243 2247 O
to 2248 2250 O
curb 2251 2255 O
coronavirus 2256 2267 O
transmissions 2268 2281 O
. 2282 2283 O

-DOCSTART- - - O

BRUSSELS 21 29 I-LOC
, 30 31 O
Dec 32 35 O
5 36 37 O
( 38 39 O
Reuters 40 47 I-ORG
) 48 49 O
- 50 51 O
European 52 60 I-ORG
Commission 61 71 I-ORG
President 72 81 O
Ursula 82 88 I-PER
von 89 92 I-PER
der 93 96 I-PER
Leyen 97 102 I-PER
said 103 107 O
on 108 110 O
Saturday 111 119 O
after 120 125 O
a 126 127 O
phone 128 133 O
call 134 138 O
with 139 143 O
British 144 151 I-MISC
Prime 152 157 O
Minister 158 166 O
Boris 167 172 I-PER
Johnson 173 180 I-PER
that 181 185 O
trade 186 191 O
negotiators 192 203 O
will 204 208 O
resume 209 215 O
talks 216 221 O
on 222 224 O
Sunday 225 231 O
. 232 233 O

“ 235 236 O
Differences 237 248 O
remain 249 255 O
. 256 257 O

No 259 261 O
agreement 262 271 O
feasible 272 280 O
if 281 283 O
these 284 289 O
are 290 293 O
not 294 297 O
resolved 298 306 O
. 307 308 O

Chief 310 315 O
negotiators 316 327 O
will 328 332 O
reconvene 333 342 O
tomorrow 343 351 O
. 352 353 O

We 355 357 O
will 358 362 O
speak 363 368 O
again 369 374 O
on 375 377 O
Monday 378 384 O
, 385 386 O
” 387 388 O
von 389 392 I-PER
der 393 396 I-PER
Leyen 397 402 I-PER
said 403 407 O
. 408 409 O

( 411 412 O
Reporting 413 422 O
by 423 425 O
Gabriela 426 434 I-PER
Baczynska 435 444 I-PER
; 445 446 O
Editing 447 454 O
by 455 457 O
Alexander 458 467 I-PER
Smith 468 473 I-PER
) 474 475 O

-DOCSTART- - - O

SYDNEY 21 27 I-LOC
( 28 29 O
Reuters 30 37 I-ORG
) 38 39 O
- 40 41 O
Australia 42 51 I-LOC
’s 52 54 O
second-largest 55 69 O
city 70 74 O
welcomed 75 83 O
its 84 87 O
first 88 93 O
international 94 107 O
passenger 108 117 O
flight 118 124 O
in 125 127 O
five 128 132 O
months 133 139 O
on 140 142 O
Monday 143 149 O
, 150 151 O
an 152 154 O
arrival 155 162 O
that 163 167 O
will 168 172 O
test 173 177 O
the 178 181 O
state 182 187 O
of 188 190 O
Victoria 191 199 I-LOC
’s 200 202 O
revamped 203 211 O
hotel 212 217 O
quarantine 218 228 O
system 229 235 O
. 236 237 O

Australia 239 248 I-LOC
has 249 252 O
since 253 258 O
March 259 264 O
closed 265 271 O
its 272 275 O
borders 276 283 O
to 284 286 O
non-citizens 287 299 O
, 300 301 O
but 302 305 O
airports 306 314 O
serving 315 322 O
Melbourne 323 332 I-LOC
, 333 334 O
Victoria 335 343 I-LOC
’s 344 346 O
capital 347 354 O
, 355 356 O
stopped 357 364 O
accepting 365 374 O
any 375 378 O
arrivals 379 387 O
in 388 390 O
late 391 395 O
June 396 400 O
after 401 406 O
an 407 409 O
outbreak 410 418 O
of 419 421 O
COVID-19 422 430 I-MISC
that 431 435 O
begun 436 441 O
at 442 444 O
two 445 448 O
hotels 449 455 O
where 456 461 O
arrivals 462 470 O
were 471 475 O
quarantining 476 488 O
. 489 490 O

More 492 496 O
than 497 501 O
20,000 502 508 O
infections 509 519 O
were 520 524 O
recorded 525 533 O
in 534 536 O
Victoria 537 545 I-LOC
when 546 550 O
hotel 551 556 O
staff 557 562 O
contracted 563 573 O
the 574 577 O
virus 578 583 O
from 584 588 O
people 589 595 O
returning 596 605 O
from 606 610 O
overseas 611 619 O
. 620 621 O

The 623 626 O
outbreak 627 635 O
has 636 639 O
been 640 644 O
widely 645 651 O
blamed 652 658 O
on 659 661 O
failures 662 670 O
of 671 673 O
private 674 681 O
contractors 682 693 O
to 694 696 O
follow 697 703 O
protocol 704 712 O
. 713 714 O

With 716 720 O
hundreds 721 729 O
of 730 732 O
people 733 739 O
expected 740 748 O
to 749 751 O
arrive 752 758 O
in 759 761 O
Victoria 762 770 I-LOC
each 771 775 O
week 776 780 O
, 781 782 O
state 783 788 O
authorities 789 800 O
have 801 805 O
said 806 810 O
police 811 817 O
officers 818 826 O
will 827 831 O
now 832 835 O
enforce 836 843 O
stricter 844 852 O
standards 853 862 O
. 863 864 O

The 866 869 O
new 870 873 O
system 874 880 O
will 881 885 O
greet 886 891 O
Australians 892 903 I-MISC
arriving 904 912 O
on 913 915 O
a 916 917 O
flight 918 924 O
from 925 929 O
Sri 930 933 I-LOC
Lanka 934 939 I-LOC
, 940 941 O
who 942 945 O
will 946 950 O
now 951 954 O
no 955 957 O
longer 958 964 O
be 965 967 O
allowed 968 975 O
to 976 978 O
leave 979 984 O
their 985 990 O
rooms 991 996 O
under 997 1002 O
the 1003 1006 O
new 1007 1010 O
hotel 1011 1016 O
quarantine 1017 1027 O
restrictions 1028 1040 O
. 1041 1042 O

The 1044 1047 O
system 1048 1054 O
is 1055 1057 O
similar 1058 1065 O
to 1066 1068 O
the 1069 1072 O
model 1073 1078 O
used 1079 1083 O
in 1084 1086 O
Sydney 1087 1093 I-LOC
, 1094 1095 O
capital 1096 1103 O
of 1104 1106 O
New 1107 1110 I-LOC
South 1111 1116 I-LOC
Wales 1117 1122 I-LOC
( 1123 1124 O
NSW 1125 1128 I-LOC
) 1129 1130 O
, 1131 1132 O
Australia 1133 1142 I-LOC
’s 1143 1145 O
largest 1146 1153 O
state 1154 1159 O
, 1160 1161 O
which 1162 1167 O
has 1168 1171 O
accommodated 1172 1184 O
thousands 1185 1194 O
of 1195 1197 O
people 1198 1204 O
returning 1205 1214 O
without 1215 1222 O
any 1223 1226 O
clusters 1227 1235 O
emerging 1236 1244 O
. 1245 1246 O

With 1248 1252 O
NSW 1253 1256 I-LOC
recording 1257 1266 O
just 1267 1271 O
one 1272 1275 O
local 1276 1281 O
infection 1282 1291 O
in 1292 1294 O
the 1295 1298 O
last 1299 1303 O
month 1304 1309 O
, 1310 1311 O
the 1312 1315 O
state 1316 1321 O
has 1322 1325 O
gradually 1326 1335 O
eased 1336 1341 O
most 1342 1346 O
social 1347 1353 O
distancing 1354 1364 O
restrictions 1365 1377 O
. 1378 1379 O

Australia 1381 1390 I-LOC
has 1391 1394 O
reported 1395 1403 O
about 1404 1409 O
28,000 1410 1416 O
cases 1417 1422 O
of 1423 1425 O
COVID-19 1426 1434 I-MISC
and 1435 1438 O
908 1439 1442 O
deaths 1443 1449 O
since 1450 1455 O
the 1456 1459 O
pandemic 1460 1468 O
began 1469 1474 O
. 1475 1476 O

Just 1478 1482 O
44 1483 1485 O
active 1486 1492 O
cases 1493 1498 O
remain 1499 1505 O
in 1506 1508 O
the 1509 1512 O
country 1513 1520 O
, 1521 1522 O
with 1523 1527 O
most 1528 1532 O
in 1533 1535 O
hotel 1536 1541 O
quarantine 1542 1552 O
. 1553 1554 O

-DOCSTART- - - O

BAMAKO 21 27 I-LOC
( 28 29 O
Reuters 30 37 I-ORG
) 38 39 O
- 40 41 O
One 42 45 O
of 46 48 O
the 49 52 O
army 53 57 O
officers 58 66 O
behind 67 73 O
an 74 76 O
August 77 83 O
coup 84 88 O
in 89 91 O
Mali 92 96 I-LOC
was 97 100 O
named 101 106 O
on 107 109 O
Saturday 110 118 O
to 119 121 O
lead 122 126 O
a 127 128 O
new 129 132 O
transitional 133 145 O
legislative 146 157 O
body 158 162 O
, 163 164 O
a 165 166 O
spokesman 167 176 O
for 177 180 O
the 181 184 O
authorities 185 196 O
said 197 201 O
. 202 203 O

The 205 208 O
appointment 209 220 O
boosts 221 227 O
the 228 231 O
number 232 238 O
of 239 241 O
military 242 250 O
figures 251 258 O
in 259 261 O
key 262 265 O
roles 266 271 O
, 272 273 O
something 274 283 O
that 284 288 O
has 289 292 O
dismayed 293 301 O
some 302 306 O
political 307 316 O
factions 317 325 O
. 326 327 O

After 329 334 O
the 335 338 O
ouster 339 345 O
of 346 348 O
President 349 358 O
Ibrahim 359 366 I-PER
Boubacar 367 375 I-PER
Keita 376 381 I-PER
on 382 384 O
Aug. 385 389 O
18 390 392 O
, 393 394 O
hopes 395 400 O
of 401 403 O
a 404 405 O
civilian-led 406 418 O
transition 419 429 O
were 430 434 O
dashed 435 441 O
by 442 444 O
the 445 448 O
appointment 449 460 O
of 461 463 O
the 464 467 O
junta 468 473 O
’s 474 476 O
leader 477 483 O
as 484 486 O
vice 487 491 O
president 492 501 O
, 502 503 O
while 504 509 O
retired 510 517 O
colonel 518 525 O
Bah 526 529 I-PER
Ndaw 530 534 I-PER
became 535 541 O
president 542 551 O
. 552 553 O

At 555 557 O
its 558 561 O
inaugural 562 571 O
meeting 572 579 O
, 580 581 O
a 582 583 O
transitional 584 596 O
council 597 604 O
of 605 607 O
121 608 611 O
members 612 619 O
has 620 623 O
now 624 627 O
approved 628 636 O
as 637 639 O
its 640 643 O
president 644 653 O
Colonel 654 661 O
Malick 662 668 I-PER
Diaw 669 673 I-PER
, 674 675 O
one 676 679 O
of 680 682 O
the 683 686 O
coup 687 691 O
’s 692 694 O
organisers 695 705 O
. 706 707 O

His 709 712 O
nomination 713 723 O
was 724 727 O
backed 728 734 O
by 735 737 O
111 738 741 O
members 742 749 O
, 750 751 O
said 752 756 O
a 757 758 O
spokesman 759 768 O
for 769 772 O
the 773 776 O
group 777 782 O
that 783 787 O
led 788 791 O
the 792 795 O
junta 796 801 O
- 802 803 O
the 804 807 O
National 808 816 I-ORG
Committee 817 826 I-ORG
for 827 830 I-ORG
the 831 834 I-ORG
Salvation 835 844 I-ORG
of 845 847 I-ORG
the 848 851 I-ORG
People 852 858 I-ORG
( 859 860 O
CNSP 861 865 I-ORG
) 866 867 O
. 868 869 O

The 871 874 O
council 875 882 O
will 883 887 O
be 888 890 O
responsible 891 902 O
for 903 906 O
voting 907 913 O
on 914 916 O
reforms 917 924 O
and 925 928 O
legislative 929 940 O
changes 941 948 O
during 949 955 O
an 956 958 O
18-month 959 967 O
transitional 968 980 O
period 981 987 O
before 988 994 O
elections 995 1004 O
are 1005 1008 O
held 1009 1013 O
. 1014 1015 O

Diaw 1017 1021 I-PER
’s 1022 1024 O
appointment 1025 1036 O
is 1037 1039 O
likely 1040 1046 O
to 1047 1049 O
anger 1050 1055 O
the 1056 1059 O
M5-RFP 1060 1066 I-MISC
coalition 1067 1076 O
of 1077 1079 O
opposition 1080 1090 O
groups 1091 1097 O
, 1098 1099 O
which 1100 1105 O
led 1106 1109 O
mass 1110 1114 O
protests 1115 1123 O
before 1124 1130 O
the 1131 1134 O
coup 1135 1139 O
and 1140 1143 O
backed 1144 1150 O
Keita 1151 1156 I-PER
’s 1157 1159 O
removal 1160 1167 O
, 1168 1169 O
but 1170 1173 O
has 1174 1177 O
voiced 1178 1184 O
alarm 1185 1190 O
over 1191 1195 O
what 1196 1200 O
it 1201 1203 O
sees 1204 1208 O
as 1209 1211 O
the 1212 1215 O
militarisation 1216 1230 O
of 1231 1233 O
the 1234 1237 O
political 1238 1247 O
sphere 1248 1254 O
. 1255 1256 O

Thirteen 1258 1266 O
out 1267 1270 O
of 1271 1273 O
Mali 1274 1278 I-LOC
’s 1279 1281 O
20 1282 1284 O
regions 1285 1292 O
are 1293 1296 O
now 1297 1300 O
governed 1301 1309 O
by 1310 1312 O
military 1313 1321 O
officers 1322 1330 O
following 1331 1340 O
new 1341 1344 O
appointments 1345 1357 O
in 1358 1360 O
November 1361 1369 O
. 1370 1371 O

Mali 1373 1377 I-LOC
’s 1378 1380 O
international 1381 1394 O
partners 1395 1403 O
and 1404 1407 O
neighbours 1408 1418 O
worry 1419 1424 O
political 1425 1434 O
instability 1435 1446 O
after 1447 1452 O
the 1453 1456 O
coup 1457 1461 O
could 1462 1467 O
derail 1468 1474 O
a 1475 1476 O
joint 1477 1482 O
fight 1483 1488 O
against 1489 1496 O
militant 1497 1505 O
groups 1506 1512 O
with 1513 1517 O
links 1518 1523 O
to 1524 1526 O
al 1527 1529 I-ORG
Qaeda 1530 1535 I-ORG
and 1536 1539 O
Islamic 1540 1547 I-ORG
State 1548 1553 I-ORG
, 1554 1555 O
which 1556 1561 O
have 1562 1566 O
grown 1567 1572 O
stronger 1573 1581 O
in 1582 1584 O
recent 1585 1591 O
years 1592 1597 O
and 1598 1601 O
made 1602 1606 O
vast 1607 1611 O
swathes 1612 1619 O
of 1620 1622 O
the 1623 1626 O
country 1627 1634 O
ungovernable 1635 1647 O
. 1648 1649 O

-DOCSTART- - - O

FILE 21 25 O
PHOTO 26 31 O
: 32 33 O
California 34 44 I-LOC
Attorney 45 53 O
General 54 61 O
Xavier 62 68 I-PER
Becerra 69 76 I-PER
speaks 77 83 O
about 84 89 O
President 90 99 O
Trump 100 105 I-PER
's 106 108 O
proposal 109 117 O
to 118 120 O
weaken 121 127 O
national 128 136 O
greenhouse 137 147 O
gas 148 151 O
emission 152 160 O
and 161 164 O
fuel 165 169 O
efficiency 170 180 O
regulations 181 192 O
, 193 194 O
at 195 197 O
a 198 199 O
media 200 205 O
conference 206 216 O
in 217 219 O
Los 220 223 I-LOC
Angeles 224 231 I-LOC
, 232 233 O
California 234 244 I-LOC
, 245 246 O
U.S. 247 251 I-LOC
August 252 258 O
2 259 260 O
, 261 262 O
2018 263 267 O
. 268 269 O

REUTERS 271 278 I-ORG
/ 279 280 O
Lucy 281 285 I-PER
Nicholson 286 295 I-PER

WILMINGTON 297 307 I-LOC
, 308 309 O
Del 310 313 I-LOC
. 314 315 O

( 317 318 O
Reuters 319 326 I-ORG
) 327 328 O
- 329 330 O
U.S. 331 335 I-LOC
President-elect 336 351 O
Joe 352 355 I-PER
Biden 356 361 I-PER
plans 362 367 O
to 368 370 O
nominate 371 379 O
California 380 390 I-LOC
Attorney 391 399 O
General 400 407 O
Xavier 408 414 I-PER
Becerra 415 422 I-PER
to 423 425 O
serve 426 431 O
as 432 434 O
secretary 435 444 O
of 445 447 O
health 448 454 O
and 455 458 O
human 459 464 O
services 465 473 O
, 474 475 O
a 476 477 O
person 478 484 O
familiar 485 493 O
with 494 498 O
the 499 502 O
decision 503 511 O
said 512 516 O
on 517 519 O
Sunday 520 526 O
. 527 528 O

-DOCSTART- - - O

FILE 21 25 O
PHOTO 26 31 O
: 32 33 O
The 34 37 O
logo 38 42 O
of 43 45 O
Mexico 46 52 I-LOC
's 53 55 O
Central 56 63 O
Bank 64 68 O
( 69 70 O
Banco 71 76 I-ORG
de 77 79 I-ORG
Mexico 80 86 I-ORG
) 87 88 O
is 89 91 O
seen 92 96 O
at 97 99 O
its 100 103 O
building 104 112 O
in 113 115 O
downtown 116 124 O
Mexico 125 131 I-LOC
City 132 136 I-LOC
, 137 138 O
Mexico 139 145 I-LOC
February 146 154 O
28 155 157 O
, 158 159 O
2019 160 164 O
. 165 166 O

REUTERS 168 175 I-ORG
/ 176 177 O
Daniel 178 184 I-PER
Becerril 185 193 I-PER
/ 194 195 O
File 196 200 O
Photo 201 206 O

MEXICO 208 214 I-LOC
CITY 215 219 I-LOC
( 220 221 O
Reuters 222 229 I-ORG
) 230 231 O
- 232 233 O
Mexican 234 241 I-MISC
President 242 251 O
Andres 252 258 I-PER
Manuel 259 265 I-PER
Lopez 266 271 I-PER
Obrador 272 279 I-PER
said 280 284 O
on 285 287 O
Monday 288 294 O
he 295 297 O
will 298 302 O
nominate 303 311 O
finance 312 319 O
ministry 320 328 O
official 329 337 O
Galia 338 343 I-PER
Borja 344 349 I-PER
to 350 352 O
serve 353 358 O
as 359 361 O
a 362 363 O
new 364 367 O
deputy 368 374 O
governor 375 383 O
of 384 386 O
the 387 390 O
central 391 398 O
bank 399 403 O
, 404 405 O
part 406 410 O
of 411 413 O
the 414 417 O
monetary 418 426 O
authority 427 436 O
’s 437 439 O
five-member 440 451 O
board 452 457 O
. 458 459 O

The 461 464 O
nomination 465 475 O
, 476 477 O
if 478 480 O
approved 481 489 O
by 490 492 O
the 493 496 O
Senate 497 503 I-ORG
, 504 505 O
would 506 511 O
give 512 516 O
Lopez 517 522 I-PER
Obrador 523 530 I-PER
’s 531 533 O
three 534 539 O
picks 540 545 O
to 546 548 O
date 549 553 O
, 554 555 O
a 556 557 O
majority 558 566 O
on 567 569 O
the 570 573 O
bank 574 578 O
’s 579 581 O
governing 582 591 O
body 592 596 O
. 597 598 O

Borja 600 605 I-PER
, 606 607 O
who 608 611 O
currently 612 621 O
serves 622 628 O
as 629 631 O
treasurer 632 641 O
, 642 643 O
is 644 646 O
set 647 650 O
to 651 653 O
replace 654 661 O
Javier 662 668 I-PER
Guzman 669 675 I-PER
, 676 677 O
known 678 683 O
as 684 686 O
one 687 690 O
of 691 693 O
the 694 697 O
central 698 705 O
bank 706 710 O
’s 711 713 O
more 714 718 O
hawkish 719 726 O
board 727 732 O
members 733 740 O
, 741 742 O
applying 743 751 O
a 752 753 O
more 754 758 O
cautious 759 767 O
approach 768 776 O
to 777 779 O
cutting 780 787 O
the 788 791 O
its 792 795 O
main 796 800 O
lending 801 808 O
rate 809 813 O
. 814 815 O

The 817 820 O
bank 821 825 O
, 826 827 O
known 828 833 O
locally 834 841 O
as 842 844 O
Banxico 845 852 I-ORG
, 853 854 O
has 855 858 O
a 859 860 O
constitutional 861 875 O
mandate 876 883 O
to 884 886 O
ensure 887 893 O
the 894 897 O
“ 898 899 O
purchasing 900 910 O
power 911 916 O
stability 917 926 O
” 927 928 O
of 929 931 O
Mexico 932 938 I-LOC
’s 939 941 O
peso 942 946 O
currency 947 955 O
. 956 957 O

Irene 959 964 I-PER
Espinosa 965 973 I-PER
is 974 976 O
currently 977 986 O
Banxico 987 994 I-ORG
’s 995 997 O
only 998 1002 O
female 1003 1009 O
board 1010 1015 O
member 1016 1022 O
. 1023 1024 O

Last 1026 1030 O
month 1031 1036 O
, 1037 1038 O
Banxico 1039 1046 I-ORG
’s 1047 1049 O
hawks 1050 1055 O
appeared 1056 1064 O
dominant 1065 1073 O
as 1074 1076 O
they 1077 1081 O
defied 1082 1088 O
expectations 1089 1101 O
and 1102 1105 O
held 1106 1110 O
borrowing 1111 1120 O
costs 1121 1126 O
steady 1127 1133 O
for 1134 1137 O
the 1138 1141 O
first 1142 1147 O
time 1148 1152 O
in 1153 1155 O
nearly 1156 1162 O
1-1/2 1163 1168 O
years 1169 1174 O
. 1175 1176 O

-DOCSTART- - - O

BRASILIA 21 29 I-LOC
/ 30 31 O
RIO 32 35 I-LOC
DE 36 38 I-LOC
JANEIRO 39 46 I-LOC
( 47 48 O
Reuters 49 56 I-ORG
) 57 58 O
- 59 60 O
Brazil 61 67 I-LOC
’s 68 70 O
government 71 81 O
is 82 84 O
in 85 87 O
advanced 88 96 O
talks 97 102 O
with 103 107 O
Pfizer 108 114 I-ORG
Inc 115 118 I-ORG
to 119 121 O
buy 122 125 O
70 126 128 O
million 129 136 O
doses 137 142 O
of 143 145 O
its 146 149 O
COVID-19 150 158 I-MISC
vaccine 159 166 O
and 167 170 O
a 171 172 O
Memorandum 173 183 O
of 184 186 O
Intent 187 193 O
should 194 200 O
be 201 203 O
signed 204 210 O
this 211 215 O
week 216 220 O
, 221 222 O
the 223 226 O
Health 227 233 I-ORG
Ministry 234 242 I-ORG
said 243 247 O
on 248 250 O
Monday 251 257 O
. 258 259 O

The 261 264 O
ministry 265 273 O
said 274 278 O
in 279 281 O
a 282 283 O
statement 284 293 O
that 294 298 O
the 299 302 O
vaccine 303 310 O
developed 311 320 O
by 321 323 O
Pfizer 324 330 I-ORG
and 331 334 O
BioNTech 335 343 I-ORG
, 344 345 O
whose 346 351 O
final 352 357 O
trial 358 363 O
results 364 371 O
showed 372 378 O
it 379 381 O
had 382 385 O
a 386 387 O
95 388 390 O
% 391 392 O
success 393 400 O
rate 401 405 O
and 406 409 O
no 410 412 O
serious 413 420 O
side 421 425 O
effects 426 433 O
, 434 435 O
will 436 440 O
be 441 443 O
delivered 444 453 O
next 454 458 O
year 459 463 O
. 464 465 O

Earlier 467 474 O
on 475 477 O
Monday 478 484 O
, 485 486 O
President 487 496 O
Jair 497 501 I-PER
Bolsonaro 502 511 I-PER
said 512 516 O
that 517 521 O
the 522 525 O
government 526 536 O
will 537 541 O
offer 542 547 O
COVID-19 548 556 I-MISC
vaccines 557 565 O
to 566 568 O
all 569 572 O
Brazilians 573 583 I-MISC
free 584 588 O
of 589 591 O
charge 592 598 O
, 599 600 O
once 601 605 O
health 606 612 O
regulator 613 622 O
Anvisa 623 629 I-ORG
gives 630 635 O
it 636 638 O
scientific 639 649 O
and 650 653 O
legal 654 659 O
approval 660 668 O
. 669 670 O

In 672 674 O
a 675 676 O
post 677 681 O
on 682 684 O
his 685 688 O
Twitter 689 696 I-MISC
account 697 704 O
, 705 706 O
Bolsonaro 707 716 I-PER
said 717 721 O
the 722 725 O
economy 726 733 O
ministry 734 742 O
has 743 746 O
assured 747 754 O
him 755 758 O
that 759 763 O
there 764 769 O
will 770 774 O
be 775 777 O
no 778 780 O
shortage 781 789 O
of 790 792 O
resources 793 802 O
to 803 805 O
administer 806 816 O
a 817 818 O
vaccine 819 826 O
to 827 829 O
everyone 830 838 O
who 839 842 O
wants 843 848 O
one 849 852 O
. 853 854 O

“ 856 857 O
Once 858 862 O
certified 863 872 O
by 873 875 O
@anvisa_oficial 876 891 I-MISC
( 892 893 O
scientific 894 904 O
guidelines 905 915 O
and 916 919 O
legal 920 925 O
precepts 926 934 O
) 935 936 O
, 937 938 O
@govbr 939 945 I-MISC
will 946 950 O
offer 951 956 O
the 957 960 O
vaccine 961 968 O
to 969 971 O
all 972 975 O
, 976 977 O
free 978 982 O
of 983 985 O
charge 986 992 O
and 993 996 O
not 997 1000 O
mandatory 1001 1010 O
, 1011 1012 O
” 1013 1014 O
Bolsonaro 1015 1024 I-PER
tweeted 1025 1032 O
. 1033 1034 O

Bolsonaro 1036 1045 I-PER
’s 1046 1048 O
tweet 1049 1054 O
came 1055 1059 O
shortly 1060 1067 O
before 1068 1074 O
the 1075 1078 O
president 1079 1088 O
of 1089 1091 O
Sao 1092 1095 I-LOC
Paulo 1096 1101 I-LOC
’s 1102 1104 O
Butantan 1105 1113 I-ORG
Institute 1114 1123 I-ORG
biomedical 1124 1134 I-ORG
center 1135 1141 I-ORG
, 1142 1143 O
Dimas 1144 1149 I-PER
Covas 1150 1155 I-PER
, 1156 1157 O
said 1158 1162 O
all 1163 1166 O
necessary 1167 1176 O
data 1177 1181 O
for 1182 1185 O
the 1186 1189 O
CoronaVac 1190 1199 I-MISC
vaccine 1200 1207 O
developed 1208 1217 O
by 1218 1220 O
China 1221 1226 I-LOC
’s 1227 1229 O
Sinovac 1230 1237 I-ORG
Biotech 1238 1245 I-ORG
Ltd 1246 1249 I-ORG
has 1250 1253 O
been 1254 1258 O
or 1259 1261 O
will 1262 1266 O
soon 1267 1271 O
be 1272 1274 O
sent 1275 1279 O
to 1280 1282 O
health 1283 1289 O
regulator 1290 1299 O
Anvisa 1300 1306 I-ORG
. 1307 1308 O

He 1310 1312 O
expects 1313 1320 O
Anvisa 1321 1327 I-ORG
to 1328 1330 O
approve 1331 1338 O
it 1339 1341 O
, 1342 1343 O
regardless 1344 1354 O
of 1355 1357 O
the 1358 1361 O
political 1362 1371 O
storm 1372 1377 O
between 1378 1385 O
Bolsonaro 1386 1395 I-PER
and 1396 1399 O
Sao 1400 1403 I-LOC
Paulo 1404 1409 I-LOC
Governor 1410 1418 O
Joao 1419 1423 I-PER
Doria 1424 1429 I-PER
over 1430 1434 O
competing 1435 1444 O
vaccines 1445 1453 O
. 1454 1455 O

“ 1457 1458 O
I 1459 1460 O
want 1461 1465 O
to 1466 1468 O
think 1469 1474 O
that 1475 1479 O
no 1480 1482 O
political 1483 1492 O
problem 1493 1500 O
is 1501 1503 O
bigger 1504 1510 O
than 1511 1515 O
people 1516 1522 O
’s 1523 1525 O
lives 1526 1531 O
, 1532 1533 O
” 1534 1535 O
Covas 1536 1541 I-PER
said 1542 1546 O
in 1547 1549 O
an 1550 1552 O
interview 1553 1562 O
with 1563 1567 O
GloboNews 1568 1577 I-ORG
. 1578 1579 O

Doria 1581 1586 I-PER
said 1587 1591 O
earlier 1592 1599 O
on 1600 1602 O
Monday 1603 1609 O
that 1610 1614 O
the 1615 1618 O
country 1619 1626 O
’s 1627 1629 O
most 1630 1634 O
populous 1635 1643 O
state 1644 1649 O
plans 1650 1655 O
to 1656 1658 O
start 1659 1664 O
vaccinating 1665 1676 O
its 1677 1680 O
population 1681 1691 O
against 1692 1699 O
COVID-19 1700 1708 I-MISC
on 1709 1711 O
Jan. 1712 1716 O
25 1717 1719 O
, 1720 1721 O
The 1722 1725 O
federal 1726 1733 O
government 1734 1744 O
expects 1745 1752 O
to 1753 1755 O
roll 1756 1760 O
out 1761 1764 O
its 1765 1768 O
own 1769 1772 O
immunization 1773 1785 O
plan 1786 1790 O
at 1791 1793 O
least 1794 1799 O
a 1800 1801 O
month 1802 1807 O
later 1808 1813 O
. 1814 1815 O

Doria 1817 1822 I-PER
’s 1823 1825 O
ambitious 1826 1835 O
timeline 1836 1844 O
comes 1845 1850 O
even 1851 1855 O
though 1856 1862 O
the 1863 1866 O
Sinovac 1867 1874 I-ORG
vaccine 1875 1882 O
has 1883 1886 O
yet 1887 1890 O
to 1891 1893 O
be 1894 1896 O
approved 1897 1905 O
by 1906 1908 O
Anvisa 1909 1915 I-ORG
. 1916 1917 O

Doria 1919 1924 I-PER
has 1925 1928 O
frequently 1929 1939 O
clashed 1940 1947 O
over 1948 1952 O
the 1953 1956 O
vaccine 1957 1964 O
with 1965 1969 O
Bolsonaro 1970 1979 I-PER
, 1980 1981 O
an 1982 1984 O
aggressive 1985 1995 O
China 1996 2001 I-LOC
critic 2002 2008 O
who 2009 2012 O
has 2013 2016 O
baselessly 2017 2027 O
dismissed 2028 2037 O
the 2038 2041 O
Sinovac 2042 2049 I-ORG
candidate 2050 2059 O
as 2060 2062 O
lacking 2063 2070 O
credibility 2071 2082 O
. 2083 2084 O
